How you doing?
It's Friday.
You know what that means?
Actually, it just means it's a nice day.
It doesn't mean anything in particular.
It just means anything that happens.
It's great.
It's even better than it was before.
That's the meaning of that.
The, uh, the Ullon.
Dude, how do I even pronounce your name, actually?
Can you tell me this once and for all?
I'm gonna call you the Ullon.
The Ullon.
Um, very angelic, huh?
Hmm.
I'll take it.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
How's everybody doing?
You're not gonna believe this.
The Ullon.
Ah, thank you.
Thank you.
Okay.
Um, today, no Coke, because I already had one for lunch.
And now I'm drinking water from a glass.
Yep.
It's water.
It's just water.
But don't let that get you down, because we're gonna be playing Terraria.
Terraria, actually, I think.
Hmm.
Employee427.
Hello, I am new to chat, but not channel.
I think that's a lie.
I've seen you here before.
Unless I have a terrible memory, which I maybe do have.
In that case, I'm sorry.
Welcome to the chat, Employee427.
Maybe it was Employee328 that I had in here last time.
I get them all mixed up.
I love water.
Do you actually... Do you go... You drink the water and you go, mmm.
God, that's good.
Is that what happens when you drink the water?
You reply to my YouTube comment once.
Maybe that's what's happening then.
I do remember your name.
Employee427.
I love that name.
It's a good name.
Yes, I do, Oliver.
Well, okay.
You know what, Hive?
You know what?
Happy birthday.
Water is awesome.
Any hydro homies in the chat?
The nectar of life.
You're not wrong.
Actrophobic gang.
Warm water tastes like shit.
I agree.
Well, not... It doesn't take like poop.
But it's not the greatest.
Let me say that.
No, water is good.
I'm just kidding.
Of course, water is amazing.
Definitely amazing.
I like lemonade.
Oh yeah, I like limonade.
Water.
Don't drink me.
No, don't worry, I'm not gonna do that.
I'm not gonna drink you.
Water needs to be hot or cold.
No in between.
Wait, nobody just drinks hot water though.
Usually they would add some kind of herb to it, right?
To give it a bit of taste.
You don't just drink hot water, that's weird.
Or maybe it's not, I don't know.
I learned recently that Italians apparently eats their morning cereal with warm milk.
And apparently that's totally normal there.
When I told them that here in Denmark we eat the cereal with cold milk, they looked at me as if I was an alien.
Can you believe that?
Am I in the wrong here?
Warm milk on cereal?
What's up, Jen?
Sarasat, my mom drinks warm water instead of cold for some reason.
The tap has always turned to hot.
But oh, alright then, well, I'm not gonna knock it.
I haven't tried it.
I gotta be honest.
I love heavy water with deuterium, Adams.
Nice.
I think we do both in Poland.
What?
It's like when I found out that some people stand up when they wipe after having taken a shit.
Apparently that's also a thing half the population does.
And that half of the population doesn't know the other half exists.
Those that sit down and wipe.
It's the same kind of scenario there.
Now fight about it.
Yeah!
It's true.
Half the people in this chat right now are standers.
The other half are sitters.
Slash poll.
Actually, am I able to do a poll?
I'm not sure.
Here's the thing, by the way, I was thinking some of you already saw this on the Discord, but I was thinking of maybe switching to Twitch one day, like as the mainstream.
There's just so many cool features there.
I've been watching a lot of streams lately on Twitch while I was sick.
And I really love all the little things they can do there.
You know, like they have the channel points and they can do polls and you can bet channel point.
It's just so much fun.
I can't do any of that here.
But anyway, it's not something that will happen anytime soon.
If it happens, I'll give you ample warning and all that stuff.
But yeah.
Will that mean the chat doesn't have to be baked into the VOD?
It could mean that.
I think that's possible then, yeah.
I mean, Twitch and YouTube both have their ups and downs, right?
The thing I really hate about Twitch is that it only goes up to 1080p.
YouTube has no limitations.
You can stream in 4k if you want.
The only reason I don't do that right now is because the delay would have to be really high, which means when I talk to you guys, that would be like, I don't know, 40 seconds or so before I see the message.
Which isn't the worst, I guess, since I don't really interact with chat, but yeah.
YouTube definitely has some advantages for sure.
Definitely.
I'm still thinking about it.
In any case, I'll let you know what I decide.
Okay, man.
It's been a while since I've been in Terraria.
It's been a while.
That's me.
I have a turtle as a pet.
I have a nice looking cape with stars on it.
Very fitting.
And I do not remember what armor I have.
It's some kind of good armor.
The robust can.
Today, it's the robust glass because there's no cans today.
We're out of cans.
All right, man.
Man, it feels like forever since I played last.
Why are there balloons?
Did I succeed in something last time?
I honestly don't remember.
Oliver got got by possessed armor.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Hold on.
The music a bit too loud.
Let me turn it down for me.
Okay.
Get rid of that.
Let me see here.
Oh, yeah, right.
I have rain bros hoodie.
These are what I'm so happy I have this system here.
I do remember all of this for sure.
Put the stuff in here.
I delete that now.
Let's see here.
Click.
What was I doing last time?
Fuck, I don't remember.
Why did I have all this?
So trying to do something special.
Oh, yeah, right.
I got this.
The Captain America shield.
Actually, a cool weapon.
I was just testing it out.
I have the titanium mask on right now.
I need to have this on because I do not want to go melee.
I want to stick to my original.
This.
So I was rocking the masterful sky fracture, the crystal storm and the golden shower.
But I tested that on the dummy.
I remember this now.
That's right.
I tried to test the whole armor reduction thing and it didn't seem to do crap.
So that's like the thing.
I think I want to try and kill some shit today.
Let's see.
Oh, we also have this issue.
We've got we've got some shit coming in here.
Look at this.
This crimson is spreading everywhere.
But it seems like it's going down here now.
So and I checked this last time.
It actually stops here.
It doesn't continue.
So I think I'm good.
I don't think it's actually going to go to my house.
Then again, it did go to this house.
But maybe there's like a difference between my main house and not my main house or like the one close to my spawn or something.
I don't know.
And then I also tested this over here.
This also doesn't seem to go into this area.
It stops right here.
So seems like the living wood is sort of a natural counter to the crimson.
Fuck yeah.
Okay, let's see here.
Eicher campfire.
Why do I have all this crap?
Let me click a magical button here.
Okay, I'm going to click a magical button.
Everything goes in.
Oh, wait, I think I wanted to test this with... is it Jeff?
Oh, my God, I remembered.
He changed his name daily because he dies daily.
What about this?
Oh, exploding bullet.
I think I did test this.
The grapefruit, fruit juice, and fruit salad.
The green slime just popped the balloon.
Hey, get out of here.
Man, I'm doing a lot of damage.
Not bad, huh?
Not bad.
And this one was like something.
Pearl sandstone.
Now, these are all like building shit.
All right.
That's what I was actually doing last time.
I was I was going to build.
But you know what?
I've changed my mind since then.
I want to fight.
I'm itching for a fight.
Let's go to the boxes here.
Melee weapons.
Put the shield in here because that is a melee weapon.
This is a door is closed.
Good.
Is he going to get in here?
Okay, we're fine.
Blocks.
Put this in here.
And that.
I think we're good.
In here, we can put like wood.
And this is a material.
Oh, I just removed something.
That's not my intention.
There we go.
Doesn't really belong there, does it?
Put it in here.
Right.
This looks good.
And then I have this guy.
And I have all my potions in here.
Fuck yeah.
Okay, now I did have weird items.
I can do this.
Hold on.
I actually want to test this.
Maybe it's different now.
I also have this one.
I don't want that.
I also have that.
Summon queenslime.
Sort.
Let's try some of these.
Oh, you know what?
Actually, if I'm going to fight a... Okay, so let me get some preparation going.
We have a statue here.
Let me put it...
I think this place is a nice place to fight.
This one's going very nice.
That would be the ideal spot for that.
Let's put it somewhere in the center.
Actually, on top of this building, huh?
There.
And then... I think I also want a campfire.
Oh, I have a campfire.
I have this one, the specialized campfire.
Let's put it on top.
Let's put it in front of here to make it look nice as well.
There we go.
Oh, what just happened?
Oh, right.
I have this item that makes stars fall from the sky whenever I take damage, which is kind of cool.
Okay, then I need this one.
Leave me that.
I'm going to put this in the house in the center here as well.
Oopsie.
Hang it there.
And now we have all these buffs.
Look, heart lamp, bass defense, cozy fire, and it's also happy turtle time.
Don't forget that, okay?
It's happy turtle time.
Now, I also want these.
Maybe just one is enough.
Maybe you don't need to spam them.
Let's spread them out a little bit.
Let's have one here, and then one on the other side of the house.
Sir, why are you in the house?
Let's put it, like, here.
Something like that.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, right.
I also need to consume actual food.
Grapefruit is only minor improvements, though.
Fuck off.
I can't even hit him.
Oh, my God.
There we go.
Now, didn't I have a food box somewhere?
Vanity, materials, potions, ores... Food!
Hey, hey, I did!
Oh, my God!
Let's put the grapefruit in here.
And let's take seafood dinner.
Not bad.
I want that.
And then we have all the potions, of course.
Let's see here.
Here's what I'm thinking, by the way.
If I summon the suspicious-looking eye, or the eye of Cthulhu, I think it's going to be way stronger now.
So I'm preparing myself.
That's why I'm doing all this.
Give me... Oh, I also want to use these today.
Random teleportation.
Okay.
Magic power, of course.
Movement speed.
We also have this.
Very nice.
Thorns.
Let's try that one.
And maybe this one, as well.
650th!
Party time's over!
Okay, man.
That was a short one.
A possessed armor is approaching.
Hold on.
A possessed armor.
I want to test the golden shower on him.
If anything has armor, it's probably the thing called possessed armor.
Right?
That's sound.
Actually, let me...
Oh, he dies from one shot.
Never mind.
Guess I'll test that later.
Let's try it, dude!
I have Cthulhu.
Oh, here he is!
Oh no, he's super weak.
Look at this shit.
Oh my god, this is not even an issue.
What the hell?
Okay, that was easy.
Are you kidding me?
Treasure bag.
Wait, how do I right-click?
Another shield.
I wonder if he drops anything else.
Actually, hold on a minute!
I can check that.
Wait a second.
Let me get to safety here.
Oh,
it's the big one.
Makes sense.
Oh, there's a 10% chance he drops a trophy.
Night time.
Oh, wait a minute!
Can I go target on me here?
I want to see the armor of the dummy.
Oh, maybe I can't.
Maybe it's just, like, you can't really check items like that.
It's technically an item, right?
And not an entity.
Okay, well, let me try again.
What if I do two at a time?
Okay, I can't.
Let me try the P. Get P'd on.
And then, is that doing anything at all?
Honestly, I'm not sure.
I also have this one.
This is great for shooting behind corners.
It can sort of bounce off the wall.
Pretty neat, huh?
Get P'd on.
Actually, the P itself is actually decent.
You know, it's actually good damage.
I like the P. Crimptain.
Dude, they actually give me money.
This is legit.
70- Hold on.
Oh, man.
They died too quick for me to test this.
Anyway, again, I'm using all of these.
Sup, dude?
Oh, he mad.
Come here.
That back looked bigger than usual.
Shield of Cthulhu.
I mean, I can sell these as well.
There we go.
That way, we clean up the inventory too.
Honestly, I can't tell whether or not this P is doing anything.
Then again, I can't really...
Maybe I could use the DPS meter here during the fight, you know?
Get out of here.
No, I didn't get a trophy.
That's so sad.
I want a trophy.
Okay, what else can we try?
Oh, I can't summon this here.
I need to be in the beehive, I think.
That's what happened last time, remember?
We can try this one.
We can also try this one.
Why can't I do it?
I can't use this one.
Wait, does it... Why can't I use this?
Gelatin Crystal.
Wait a minute.
Can I maybe check this in the thingy?
Slime.
King Slime.
Surface.
Slimes normally aren't intelligent, but occasionally they merge together to become a powerful force.
To swallow all things.
Yeah, I don't think I have an entry because I haven't met it yet.
Hold on.
Queen Slime.
Maybe it's called something else here.
Oh, Queen B.
Seems like they alter up trophies, but it's only 10% chance.
Maybe it only spawns in a different biome.
Let me experiment a little bit, actually.
It would be a great place for the Queen to be.
A slimy area.
I don't even know.
I'm just gonna walk from left to right and test everything.
Yeah.
Is this spreading?
Hold on.
Oh wait, it is!
I think it's further down now, look!
Wait a minute, what about...
Okay, this one is still there.
Oh my god, these things do so much damage.
They took one quarter of my HP just now.
I wasn't looking for like a split second there.
Can I summon it here?
I can't.
By the way, last time I fought the king, it was here.
I remember this.
Oh, but back then this was desert.
So maybe I need to be in the desert.
Honestly, I have no clue.
I'm just spitballing right now.
Give me that.
Maybe here.
Ah, there we go!
Queen's 28,000 HP!
P on you!
Oh my god.
I'm taking damage here.
Bro, this has a lot of HP.
Okay, dude.
I have trouble figuring out what's happening on the screen in this game.
There's so much crap on the screen.
I can't tell what belongs to me and what belongs to the enemy.
Like all the particles, all the colors, all the bullshit.
It's fucking difficult, man.
Also, I was buffed up pretty hard just now and I lost all those buffs.
That's unfortunate.
But now I know I can only do that in... I forgot the name of that place.
But in that biome.
Hey, you there.
Thank you.
Bro, I thought I was strong.
I thought I built some cool armor here.
Apparently not.
I just die instantly.
It's weird to me how... So the boss I killed just before was a cakewalk.
This one, there's no in-between.
It's just like either you stomp or you get stomped.
There's no in-between here.
It's weird how that works.
Oh, I just realized, by the way.
I don't have any good healing... Oh, I do have healing potions, never mind.
I thought I only had the minor one.
What the... Get out of here, you fucker.
There we go.
Look how they open their shell and then sort of spit the lasers.
Hey.
What?
What just killed me?
A wraith.
I didn't even see it.
I have no idea where that guy was.
Hold on, I need to adjust the volume here.
Okay, that's better.
Okay, drink a potion.
I'm gonna grab the statue with me now.
I actually forgot that.
I want the best statue and I also want the campfire.
Give me this and that.
And I guess I can try with one of these as well.
I'm not sure if it'll work in that biome, but it's worth trying.
Why did these guys lose HP?
What happened here?
Maybe a slime.
Also, I didn't even test my items here.
Are they okay?
Increased magic damage.
Jump height.
Ah, the chisel is shit.
I need to replace that.
Give me some speed at least.
Or that one.
Immunity to knock back.
It gives a little bit of defense.
I think this one may be better.
Speed and mobility is just such an important thing.
I have titanium gear on right now.
Wait, why do I have this on?
I want this on.
Right.
Yeah, I want 25% reduced.
Okay, that's a big change right now.
That's gonna mean a lot.
That's gonna be important.
The problem is, fighting the Queen there.
There's not really much surface area to work with.
So maybe I will tunnel through here.
Wait a minute.
Technically, this part is also this biome.
Hold on, what was the name of this biome?
I need to check again.
I can see that some of these prefer this place.
I think it's the Hello.
Okay, get rid of these guys.
Now place this.
Yeah, it works!
Cool.
Put that there.
And then we're gonna hang our... Oh, did I forget the lantern?
Crab cakes.
Maryland crab cakes.
Did I actually?
Oh no.
By the way, I only have one more try on this.
It's not like I can keep trying either.
It's like, you summoned this shit?
And you just die.
And you didn't even get a chance to process what the fuck just happened, you know?
Anyway, I'm gonna go back and grab the healing thingy, because it's quite important.
Look how fast I am now with that item.
It does a world of difference.
The fleeting magi luminescence.
In fact, let me check if I have something better while I'm here.
What would be great for this?
Let's place damage per second.
More... Hey, wait!
What happens if I wear this?
We're gonna try that.
That could also... nah, reduced mana cards is not really that big of a deal.
Nothing in here seems good.
What kind of damage does the queen slime do, I wonder?
Let's place how many monsters we can kill.
Maybe that.
No, it's also terrible.
I could stack this as well.
Hmm, I'm not sure.
I think I'm doing okay already with my items.
Wait, brain of confusion.
That could be good.
Maybe we replace... Oh, it's a tough call here.
I mean, the speed is good.
But if I'm gonna be honest here, I will get hit.
You know, I am just gonna get hit from time to time.
And this will actually give a chance of just mitigating the hit completely.
Which would be kind of crazy.
He's thinking about fishing.
Well, me too, buddy.
Me too.
That's all I want to do.
I just want to fish.
Okay, you're not gonna annoy me?
I was really afraid this Crimson would just fuck up my house, but it seems like we're okay.
For now, at least.
It is slowly spreading downwards.
But I guess I'll have to keep an eye on it for now.
And deal with it when we get to that point.
Wait, I'm not quite sure how to deal with it.
Because the fucking powder that Rosalva sells is useless.
It is insanely useless.
Like, what is the... what is the point there?
You know what I could do, actually?
Worst case.
I could relocate stuff over here.
Because this is like the good, right?
And this is the evil.
And it doesn't seem to... you know?
This would be the place.
Put this here.
Let's put the slime banner there as well, actually.
That can't be bad, right?
Campfire.
There we go.
And that seems good to me.
Put it down.
Did I just do 800... no, no, 86 damage.
I thought I did 800 damage.
Okay.
How do I want to fight this?
Hmm.
I guess I could do it over here.
I mean, it's not... I can just summon it here and then walk to the left, I guess.
I guess I can drag it to the place I want it to be.
Right?
Or I could just make a bunch of fucking platforms, but I don't want to fucking do that, man.
That seems insane.
Yeah, this is a troublesome place to fight anyway, because we're right next to Crimson.
And there's going to be enemies everywhere, so I have to go to the right in any case.
Maybe I'll take these with me and put this on the right side.
Yeah.
Let's go over here instead.
We could do it on top of the mountain.
That would be kind of epic.
But this seems more flat and doable right here.
Actually, this is a great place.
Except these guys are annoying.
Oh my god, I can't hit shit with this.
Let me see what's over here.
There's so many of these somewhere.
Fleeting fast cloak.
Oh, clock!
I thought it was a fleeting fast cloak.
Pixie dust.
I forgot what that's for.
Okay, now the Crimson starts again.
That's bad.
It's got to be here.
I could make a little tunnel through here, at least.
That's something.
We go like this.
Oh wait, I have to actually go down here.
You have to cut the tree from the bottom.
Get off!
There we go.
And start digging.
It's so weird being back in Terraria.
I've played a lot of inscriptions and Starcraft lately.
So seeing something like this is just weird to me.
That's a unicorn!
Hey!
You go and die!
Give me your horn!
Thank you!
Okay.
Sir!
There we go.
There we go, like that.
I guess I can move a bit of this.
Hey!
No!
Get off!
Here's the thing, by the way.
Oh, I think I may have just figured something out.
The Queen's Lime bounces on top of things, right?
If I'm underneath here, I'm protected.
Right?
That makes sense to me.
It's not actually gonna fly through walls like some of the other bosses.
A wild, fast clock.
Man, there's just clocks everywhere here.
The hell?
Okay, let's just fucking go, huh?
Let's just go.
Put statue.
Put this... Can we hang it on a branch?
Shit, we can't do that.
We can put it in here though.
There we go.
And this one, we can put there.
Just place it.
Let's put the slime banner.
Campfire.
Hey!
There we go.
I forgot to eat the seafood dinner too, by the way, last time.
I will not forget this time.
I also have a chocolate.
Huh.
No, this is 14 minutes.
There's no way this is gonna be more than 14 minutes.
In fact, I'll probably die within 30 seconds.
So, let's just consume that.
There we go.
And then, we do magic potion.
Thorns.
Let's have swiftness.
And these things are gonna be annoying during the fight, for sure.
What else do I have?
Sonar, heart reach.
I don't really have that much more.
I should get one of those potions of defense, but I don't have it right now.
And I have to go through asking the guide for a million items.
Figure out what their ingredients are and shit, and grab the ingredients, make it as... Nope.
Not happening right now.
Let's just do it.
Man, there's so many pixies.
Uh... Oh man, I have to get rid of this.
Here we go.
Wish me luck.
We're gonna... Oh no, not now.
Oh no, it's yellow!
Oh, that totally works on that!
Oh my god, I'm losing a lot of HP.
Oh!
It spawned right on top of me.
Okay, okay, okay, I see, I see, I see.
I'm gonna kite it over here for a second.
Let's just see what it does.
Okay, it shoots balls.
Gotcha.
It shoots the balls.
Oh, I'm dying here, for sure.
I can't even... I'm getting... I should get the immune to pushback, for sure, because I'm getting knocked back a lot here.
Oh, is it gonna teleport that down to me now?
There's so many small things everywhere!
I don't know, I don't know what's damaging me!
Fuck!
This is so chaotic!
I got it to like 70%, though.
That's not bad.
Way better attempt than last time.
Alright.
Fucking bosses in this game, dude.
Okay, quick stack.
Oh, look at that.
That is just fantastic.
I'm gonna try... Let's try the mechanical skull.
Let's see what that does.
Oh, but I don't have my items here.
I guess I gotta go pick them up first.
Hold on.
What is that?
Oh!
Right, I got this!
I kind of forgot about that.
Right!
Ha!
Totally forgot I had that.
Pearlwood!
That's new.
I wonder how that looks.
If it looks good or bad.
Alright, we're gonna try and see if we can find a little bit of an easier enemy.
That thing is fucking crazy.
God,
I wish the pylon network here is actually working.
I wish to have it everywhere.
I have one here.
One over here.
No, actually, do I?
No, it's down there.
It's down there.
But I want one on the surface, but for some reason I couldn't get it up and running over there.
And then I want something in between these two pylons as well.
Like right here.
Or maybe even up here would be kind of cool.
On one of the floating islands.
Not too shabby.
In fact, I'm just gonna try and see if I can summon the skeleton guy here.
Maybe it works.
Okay, let's see.
Eat this.
Honestly, it doesn't really matter if I buff up all the way.
This is just mostly a test to see what the fuck I'm getting myself into.
Let me get the basics here.
God damn it.
Hey!
Okay, let's try it.
Doesn't work.
Maybe it's only during the night.
Let's try this one.
Summon's a pirate invasion.
Pirates are approaching from the east.
Okay.
Wait, is it at my house?
Oh, it probably is, right?
It's always in the house area when this stuff happens.
I forgot to take the thingies with me.
Actually, we have another bad statue here.
That's fine.
Okay, from the east.
Where are they?
Bring it on, bitches.
Fucking pirates.
How dangerous can that be?
I feel like I need an enemy that I can actually beat.
And I'm not talking about the I.F.
Cthulhu.
I'm talking about something...
Maybe a little bit harder than the I.F.
Cthulhu, you know?
Not something in... Oh, wait.
They said east.
I gotta go east.
Let's go east.
Oh, here we go.
Pirate invasion.
Cleared 0%.
Where are they?
The deck... Here they come.
Holy shit.
There's a lot.
Whoa.
I'm funneling them.
Oh, wait.
It doesn't go through the doors or... There we go.
What's up, guys?
What's going on?
How you doing?
Kill them all.
How do I have mana for this?
I don't.
Okay, okay.
Let's just chill for a second.
Let me try and pee on them.
Oh, no, my people are dying!
Is that helping?
Look, they're definitely yellow now.
That's gotta mean they have the debuff.
Look.
Nice one, Fantasia.
Get peed on.
Fuck you.
What are these guys?
They're kinda stuck in there.
Look, that's fine with me.
Gotta parrot.
Let me see her.
Oh, no, no!
Don't you fucking touch her.
Hold on.
Can I actually heal?
I'm gonna test something here.
When I take damage, I'm gonna try and see if I can use her to heal.
It's gonna seem a little crazy, maybe.
Mid fight, but... Maurice!
Oh, no.
I instinctively used my potion.
No, she's dead!
Never mind.
Fuck.
Eleven percent cleared.
Okay, this is not too bad.
This ain't too bad.
I like it.
I can actually win.
Yay!
This is a good spot I'm in here.
It's like they're getting Star?
Oh, wait, never mind.
I thought her name was Star.
Oosh.
Hey, guys, come on.
Come on, now.
Oh, they can't get in.
How cute.
I like this weapon here, because it bounces around all the halls in here.
The parrot, though.
Oh, you know what?
I should have summoned a little bit.
I can still summon some things.
Uh-oh.
I should probably close that door over there.
Close it.
Yeah, look, they can't get in.
They suck.
I want to test something.
Does this go up even though I don't do anything?
Probably not, right?
I have to kill things for this to go up.
There's no timer here at all.
I can't pee through the wall, unfortunately.
Ah, get peed on.
Although, they're super confused.
Oh, they do damage.
They are shooting hard projectiles here.
Hmm.
How am I gonna do this?
Let me make a hole up here and do a bit of the... Oh, okay, they're shooting me.
Let me zoom out a bit so I can see what the fuck's going on.
Who's shooting?
Oh!
Okay, they're right below me.
I want to put the raining stuff here.
Oh, it's not here though.
How am I gonna do this?
Honestly,
if I'm at good range, they're not really... Okay, he's shooting.
Yeah, I just have to be at good range here.
Give me all that stuff.
This ain't too bad.
Okay, there's some over here as well.
Let me... Fuck you!
Uh-oh.
Okay, they're gonna come up here.
This is a problem.
Okay, this is actually fine.
We're fine.
This is the ultimate home invasion.
Holy crap.
Dope!
Pee!
Pee on everyone!
Get outta here!
Fucking pirates.
Pirate Corsair.
Nice.
Uh-oh, that's scaring me a little bit.
Yeah, look at that.
Totally debuffed.
I'm killing this dude!
Uh-oh, there's projectiles.
Who are you?
A captain!
Oh, he has a lot of HP!
Hey!
Oh, he's shooting.
Fast.
Uh-oh.
I need to bounce these off the wall.
Look at that, that's how we do it.
Oh, he's fucked!
Get fucked, dude!
Yeah!
There we go!
Oh, what's that?
Oh, it's one of mine.
One of mine, it's one of mine.
We're fine.
Get peed on.
P-P-P-P-P.
Emergency urine.
Fuck all they all.
Dude, I'm loving this bouncy weapon here.
Pee!
Urine!
43% cleared!
This is a long one.
Wow.
I guess I am killing it kinda slowly here.
But, I'm playing it safe.
I am playing it safe.
Dude, this is a great little choke point I've got him in here.
Hell yeah!
Peed on!
Let me try this a bit.
Oh yeah, it's a little bit scary.
This one is a little bit more assured that I get some hits in here.
Oh god.
Heel up!
What is the confetti shit everywhere?
Oh, is it the party girl?
Get out of here!
Uh oh!
Oh!
Huh?
No, the party girl has died!
Bro, the urine is actually insane.
Pirate crossbower.
It's just hanging out up there.
What the hell is happening?
Oh god.
Fuck you!
We gotta close some doors here.
Good thing the pirate thingy can't get in here.
Pee!
Oh!
I'm actually getting low.
Why's the door open?
Maybe I opened it.
Oh god, they're shooting.
Just murder them all.
Pee time!
Let me regen some mana here.
Okay, they're having trouble hitting me in here.
Dude, the boss though.
Look at the HP.
I'm scared of fighting him.
The percentage is going up right now while I'm killing these.
Maybe I can get to a point where I've killed all these subordinates and I only have the boss left.
That's my hope right now.
Oh god.
Get these fucking thingies out of here.
Carrots?
I was about to say parrots!
I feel blessed that this fucking pirate ship isn't going after me.
I have a feeling it's going to do more than a little bit of damage.
Hey!
Get out of my house!
70% clear!
These projectiles are killing me.
I need to close some doors.
There.
Closed.
Let's just hang back for a minute.
Let's heal up a bit.
Let's chill.
Let me refresh this.
I don't know how long I have left, but let's just do it.
Okay.
Eight seconds for potion.
Am I not in range of a lantern thingy?
Maybe I'm not.
Golden sink.
Nice.
Put it there.
Look at it up there.
Flying Dutchman!
Oh, cool.
All right.
Flying Dutchman, huh?
Heal?
Okay.
I think we're back in action.
I'm going to open this door and go up.
Uh-oh.
I'm taking some damage here.
Actually, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
This is a better position to be in up here.
This is what I prefer.
Yeah, this is definitely better.
It's more efficient this way.
All right.
A superior cutlass.
Cool.
I'm going to check that out.
Oh, my God.
How did this guy get up here, by the way?
Suddenly, he was in my quarters.
Bro, maybe you're spamming?
The P is also viable.
It's not as good, is it?
Uh-oh.
Oh, and I get in through the top!
I'm almost dead.
I need to hang back.
I need to close the door.
Shit!
Close the door!
Okay.
Let's chill.
We're chilling.
Whoo!
Whoo, I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
82% cleared.
Oh, my God.
I need to heal faster.
Do I have anything I can heal with?
Hey, I can heal it.
Hang these.
Golden.
Golden clock!
Put it down!
Emergency golden clock!
Ah, I can't put it anywhere!
Increase his coin?
Pig of range?
Heal?
Nice.
Okay, we're back.
Get Pete on!
Where'd you come from?
Oh, wait.
He came up through the top.
Let me actually close that off.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, for now, let's close this.
Oh, they're jumping out of the ship!
Aha!
Okay.
Get Pete on.
And now we hang back up here again.
Oh, God.
Pete!
Dude, that thing does so much damage.
Is he gonna shoot me?
Are you gonna shoot me?
Okay, 91%.
Oh, my God.
Look at the damage from me here.
This is actually great.
But I'm about to die.
I'm almost dead.
I'm gonna play it safe again.
Oh, shit, dude.
Oh, this guy has a bow.
Get rid of her.
There we go.
Nice.
How much until healing?
Now.
Push!
Okay, P is good.
The P is good.
Urine is working.
Okay.
Get all this loot.
Yep, okay.
97%.
Holy crap.
I keep thinking this is an enemy, but it's just Ella.
99%.
Get Pete on.
Shotty something.
Fuck yeah.
The pirates have been defeated.
Now, scurry off, fuckers!
Uh-oh, don't hit me with that.
Ah!
Oh, God.
That did a lot of damage.
I thought you were done.
Please just die.
Okay.
They keep coming.
Wait a minute.
It's still here.
Okay, hold on a second then.
Let me heal up.
And then I'm gonna go try and attack the ship here.
Can I make a little shooting hole?
Ha-ha!
Hey, fucker!
Hold on, let me do one more.
Oh!
It's aiming its guns.
P on it.
Oh!
Dude, this is solid.
Bro, this is great.
Honestly, maybe the P is the best.
The fact that it goes through everything is actually nuts.
Okay, get some more mana here.
Fuck you!
I'll piss on you and your grave.
Or whatever the quote goes.
Kill it.
There it is!
Yeah!
Ain't nobody coming in my house!
Fuck yeah, man!
Get rid of these torches.
Heck yeah!
Who's the man?
How many did we lose?
Let's get a head count.
Actually, people are sort of alive.
It's not too bad.
It's not the worst.
Cool.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, get out of here.
You know what?
Let's put on this thing.
Let's be friendly to, uh, slimes here.
And you!
Get away.
Marty!
Look, change his name every day.
Rip Jeff.
Dude, the parrot's here.
The first thing I think of when I hear this name is...
Doc Brown going...
MARTY!
Okay, let's see.
What do we get?
Uh...
Golden items.
I guess they've been raiding, huh?
Superior cutlass?
Melee item?
Golden...
I could do it again, but I don't want to do that again.
Shoddy cutlass.
But no, I already had golden sofa.
Guarding gold ring.
Increases coin pickup range.
Golden platforms, red hat.
Yeah, alright.
I guess I got some money out of it.
And if I ever want a really golden themed place, I can now do that.
Okay.
What is next?
Actually,
I'm going to give that to Marty.
I have discovered my love for this weapon during this.
Lucky coin.
Okay.
Which I can make a coin ring out of.
Hitting enemies will sometimes drop extra coins.
I guess I get this from the pirates as well.
I can't imagine where else I would get that.
Pip!
Has arrived!
Alright, cool.
Now we did that.
Now we can try the mechanical skull.
Actually, let me clean my inventory first.
So far we've had one loss.
Actually, two losses to the queen.
And one win against pirates.
Next up!
Mechanical skull.
Skeletron Prime, it says.
And I'm excited.
Am I though?
Maybe I'm not.
Maybe I am.
You'll never know.
Uh, what?
In here.
Do I have any block?
No, you know what?
Construction, this is where this shit goes.
In fact, I need another chest.
Take this chest and put it up here instead.
This is another construction.
Rename it.
We don't have enough room.
I'm definitely making a golden room at some point.
With a golden sofa and all the golden...
etchings, you know.
All the good stuff.
Like this.
Sailor pants?
That's a vanity.
And you go.
Ah, okay.
These weapons...
I already have one of them.
I can sell one of them here.
This one?
Let's try it.
It's a weapon.
It's a melee weapon.
What a surprise.
Let's put it in the melee box.
There you go.
This one will be sold.
And this one goes in materials.
No, accessories.
I have clocks.
Let's sell one of them.
Actually, I have many clocks.
Precise or fleeting?
I think I want to keep the fleeting.
And then sort.
There we go.
This is all getting sold.
And then in Michelinius, we can put the pirate map in.
And this one.
Maria, the zoologist, has arrived.
Cool.
It's 4pm.
Treven?
You're the new Maurice.
Buy this.
What was the condition here?
I couldn't just do it anywhere, right?
No, I can't do it here.
I think it needs to be Knight.
Or maybe I need to go where the old man was.
No, actually, it needs to be Knight.
Remember the old man?
It's got to be something like that.
So maybe I'll prepare for that.
While we wait for Knight, it's actually soon.
I'm going to see if I can't quickly...
scrounge up some potions here, or make some.
Bottled water.
Now we ask Marty.
Marty!
We've got to go back to the future!
I need... I need defense.
Iron skin.
Daybloom and lead.
Do I have daybloom?
That's the big question right now.
Potion ingredients?
I have one.
Shit, I gotta go find some daybloom.
How about we just go around and collect some flowers for a bit?
So, daybloom, water and...
Fuck, I forgot the last thing.
Oh, lead, lead.
Or...
Lead...
Gimme one.
There it is, there it is.
Dum, dum, dum.
Okay, whoa!
I had my potion crafting station over here.
There.
There you go.
Nice!
Quick stack.
Now I have that.
Put it in.
And potions, put this in.
Very good.
Do I have anything else in here I may want to take with me?
Maybe the regeneration.
Now, the thing is, I want to leave at least one of them in here.
One of each.
That was the point.
So that I can always click the button and make it auto-sort.
You know, auto-stack, I mean.
Heartreach, let's take one of these, I guess.
I think we already have one, but that's okay.
Gravitation...
Water...
Hey!
I have an idea.
I could just fight a boss in the water with water walking.
Wouldn't that be awesome?
Hello?
That seems pretty cool, man, I'll take it.
And I think that's it.
For now.
This is good.
Okay!
I'm off!
I am going to grab my lantern.
I think I left it somewhere to the right.
The statue here, let's just leave that here, that's actually nice.
I hate these things with a passion.
I hate these things with a mild passion.
A very mild one, it's not bad at all.
Let's replace...
Where's my running?
There we go.
I need running.
By the way, I think this defense that I got here, you know the shields that rotate around me, I think they helped me a lot during the last fight.
I'm not sure they did, but I think they did.
Because I saw the effect constantly on me.
And it's got to be good, right?
It's got to be good.
Okay,
here we go.
Grab that.
Then we walk over here, grab this one.
That one, that one, that one.
That one, thank you.
Actually, we can leave the banner here, because I'm going to come back here later.
And try and punish the queen.
Yep.
We can actually do this.
Can I?
Do I have a diamond I was about to say?
A little pylon, I don't.
But I do have this next best thing.
This is the poor man's pylon, the PMP.
And don't you forget it.
Ah.
Can we go faster?
Come on.
Oops.
I'm sorry.
There we go.
Look at the lantern celebrating my victory.
Against the pirate invasion that I brought upon us.
Well, I decided to bring them upon us, you know, so it's not really.
I just fixed the problem that I caused, really.
I'm not a hero.
What was that?
Is elemental.
Isn't that new?
I have no memory of this.
You know what?
I like peeing.
Are they dropping anything good?
Bro, it's actually working.
Oh, I'm chilled.
That's why I'm so slow.
Okay, this is annoying me.
We go back up here.
I can't reach.
Go.
I just can't reach it.
Why am I so quick?
Oh, right.
I forgot about this.
Oh, yeah.
I have this thing.
Completely forgot about that.
What the fuck?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no.
This is...
Man, look at all the shit I made here.
Actually, I could use this.
I made this a long time ago.
Actually, it feels like an eternity ago.
This looks fucking horrible.
Look at all this crap.
Why are there so many enemies?
Oh, my God.
The Crimson.
It has gone all the way.
Has it been like this all the time here?
I don't remember if it's been this bad last time as well.
I feel like it hasn't.
But then again, I do remember fighting these guys here, and they were very annoying while I was dealing with the last skeleton guy.
So, not quite sure.
Okay, let's hang up some stuff.
There we go.
Let's do this.
Oh, we already have one of these.
That's fine.
Seafood dinner.
Fish is good for you, or so they say.
They say many things, don't they?
Okay.
Now, there's way too many enemies.
This is so bad.
I need a potion of invisibility.
Potion of invisibility.
There you go.
You can't see me now.
Let's try it.
Drink potions.
That one.
Cool, cool, cool, cool.
Let's just fucking try it, boys.
Yep, it works.
Oh, okay, here we go.
Get Pete on.
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah, he's doing some damage here.
Oh!
Oh, God.
Oh, there's no way.
There's no way.
Hop,
hop, hop, hop, hop, hop, hop.
Get Pete on.
I'm taking way too much damage.
I don't even know what I'm hitting, man.
It's so chaotic.
Oh, I have no more mana.
That's the problem.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, that's no way, man.
I fucking knew it was gonna end like this.
I knew it was gonna end like this.
This game is so fucking binary when it comes to difficulty.
It's unreal.
I have never experienced something like this in a video game.
It's fucking crazy.
It's either a walkover or a trip to the shed with the old grandpa, you know?
Okay, let's see.
I don't think I want to try that again.
In fact, I can't, because I used my item, so I cannot even try again.
Which is unfortunate.
So instead, I'm just gonna go explore.
Maybe we can fucking find some better armor, because this armor sucks dick.
Like, I take three hits and I'm dead.
I thought this was supposed to be good armor, man.
It's titanium.
It's like the highest grade of the grade of ore.
But apparently that's not enough.
Sort my items.
Nice.
I forgot the past statue!
That's why I lost.
That's the only reason why I lost.
Next time, I'll remember that.
In fact, let's put it in here.
This is good to have in here.
This is like utility potions and stuff like...
I just deleted it.
God damn it!
Why is there a difference between... Why do we have to hold control when you sell items and shift when you stack?
See, that's confusing.
I have an extra.
Put it in here.
Sort.
Why are there torches in here?
Oh, right, because I wanted to use the Eicher torches first.
Get out of here.
Okay.
What is my goal right now?
Actually, yeah, let's talk to Marty and ask.
What the fuck I'm supposed to be doing in this game.
Where are thou?
You're there.
Marty?
Yes, there is something you can help me with, in fact.
Help!
For a nurse to move in, you might want to increase your maximum life.
Thanks.
Wizard, found him.
That's Rosalva, right?
Stylist, whatever.
Oh, tortured soul down in the underworld, sure looks familiar.
Have you tried using purification powder on him?
I have not.
Let's do that right now.
Where is Rosalva?
There she is.
Let's try that.
Go here.
Then we need to go purchase some purifying powder.
Purification powder.
Hey.
This area is so weird.
I wonder if there's more biomes that I haven't even found yet.
I doubt it.
Because the map is not even that big, you know?
Like, it's limited.
How many things there can be?
Up here?
Nah, these guys are annoying.
Oh, I save you.
Rosalva?
Be safe, Terraria needs you.
What's the status?
11% hallow and 19% crimson, you have a lot of work to do.
Can I convert things into hallow?
Can I increase that number?
Is there a hallow powder?
I'll just gonna take a bunch of this.
In fact, I need it anyway.
Because of the crimson.
How's that doing, by the way?
Okay, it doesn't seem like it has gone further down yet, so it's like very slow.
Sign the nerdy slime.
I like that.
Where's your friend, Cosine?
I want to fish and you... No, I'm not.
Shut the fuck up.
I'm gonna go down into the underworld.
To torture a soul.
I mean, purify a tortured soul.
Yep, that's what I'm doing.
Maybe he's at a very special location.
I'm just gonna go down from here, cause why not?
I forgot what this was.
I think this is a cobalt.
Yeah, it is.
Steel trap.
Pattern recognition, master number one.
Pattern master 4,000.
That's what they call me down at the center.
Of advanced hallucinations.
1984.
Top of the class.
People know me.
I get around, you know?
I don't know what the fuck I'm on about.
I need to find the way down.
Here.
This way.
Come on!
Also, let's equip the proper weapons.
I really wanted to kill that guy just now.
And I did it, and I feel good.
Let me go here.
Hey, what do you have in your...
He had a thing in his hand.
Further down.
Here.
What the hell?
Oh, a tortoise!
That's what it sounds like.
Turtle shell.
Oh!
I don't remember if I ever found that.
Definitely gonna show that to Marty.
Oopsie!
See ya.
I am going to look for...
more biomes as I travel here.
Gimme this.
You know what I just realized?
Ah, dude.
What if there's a way to...
I'm gonna present a theory now that makes zero sense because it's based on nothing.
It's purely my imagination.
I'm just gonna pretend that's the case.
I think there may be, and it would make sense, that in the Crimson, somewhere inside there's a...
there's some kind of block that is the cause of the spread of the Crimson.
Such that when I remove that, the whole thing becomes nice and green.
Because how else can you do it?
Like, the fucking powder is useless.
There's no way you're supposed to use the powder.
That's just crazy.
So there's gotta be some mechanic to revert the whole thing and heal the world.
Who killed the world, you know?
What am I looking for?
I'm looking for the Obsidian.
Potion.
Oh, do I not have one?
Goddammit!
Alright, we're just gonna have to be careful.
Demon banner, thanks.
So here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna start from one end to the other, and we're gonna find this dude.
No matter what.
Oh!
Whoopsie-daisy.
I hate him.
Get rid of him.
Okay, let's be on the lookout for a dude here.
Or a dude dead.
I don't know.
Maybe there's somewhere up here- Oh!
Pussy!
Almost fell to my death.
I'm really looking here.
This is Archer.
Not quite what I'm looking for, but it'll have to do.
Dude, I am taking damage from things I don't even know what is.
Hello?
What is going on?
No clue.
What just happened?
I have no idea how I just died.
I guess I died to poison, sure, but what just took all of my HP?
Fuck!
I don't wanna go down that way again.
Let's take this path over here.
At least that's almost completely straight.
Straight down.
Verticolius Maximus.
Is what this, I don't even know, pipe will be known as.
Henceforth.
Verticalius Maximus.
Because it's maximum vertical.
Oopsie!
We overshot.
Okay, down we go.
Hold on, what if I unequip?
I wonder if I can fall faster.
Oh, what the hell is that?
Why is that the source of the crimson?
Why does that look like that?
Wait a minute.
Okay, it doesn't say anything when I mouse over.
I just wanna check.
Oh, we've got these guys over here as well.
Oh, nevermind, it's nothing.
The party girl has arrived.
Once again.
Nice.
They are peeing on me.
Oopsie!
I'm out of mana.
Actually, it's an issue.
There we go.
This guy is dead.
Soul of knights.
Okay, let's take it slow.
How do I fucking get to the root of this crimson problem?
That is like the big question.
Amadusa?
Pocket mirror.
I think I have one of those already.
I don't!
Immunity to petrification.
What did I have?
I have magic mirror or something.
Cool.
They can probably be combined with other things to be immune to all kinds of stuff.
Is this new music?
Oh nice, look at this.
We have like a little outpost here.
Okay, where's this tortured soul?
In fact, what if I just start throwing the purification powder on everything I see?
Where is it?
Where did I put it?
There it is.
What if I can purify certain enemies?
Probably would be in the crimson area, if anything, right?
Tortured soul.
Our stow here.
I don't even know where to look.
Probably one of these houses, right?
Maybe he's like being held in the cellar or something, that would make sense.
Maybe he spawns like randomly in one of these houses or something.
You get away from me.
Nothing down here.
Should I be using a potion that highlights enemies and stuff?
It also highlights friends, right?
But just in a different color or something?
Or just old creatures?
Honestly, I don't remember.
Let's see.
Spillunker, treasure and ore.
No, that's not it.
Hard reach.
Get out of here.
No.
I don't have anything like that.
Tortured soul.
Hold on, maybe there's an enemy called a tortured soul.
I should mouse over everything.
Maybe I have... Oh, look, it's one of these!
Oh, should I try?
Let's try it.
What happens if I do this now?
I have a voodoo doll again.
These things are annoying me.
Okay, so I actually started over here last time.
I remember this.
Because I built this.
Let me just scan these houses real quick.
I'm not seeing a person, per se.
Dude, what if the tortured soul is the wall of flesh?
Think about that.
Oh!
Fuck you.
Delete that from existence.
Oh, there's a little fucking bat.
Giving me such a fright.
This lava can't hurt me.
No.
Okay, let's heal up.
And wait a bit.
I'm actually gonna try and kill this again.
Fuck, I'm gonna go to the right and go to the healing station that I made.
Also, my items, are we good on that?
Oh, wait, I definitely need obsidian potion if I'm gonna do this.
There's no way I'm doing that now.
I need obsidian potion.
Absolutely.
Absolutely fucking lootly.
Also, I came here with one purpose in mind.
Let's try and finish that.
I'm not taking the chance here.
Anyone down here?
Oh, that's a piano.
A very devilish piano.
Oh, wait, I also have platforms here.
tortured soul.
Hello.
Where are they?
Maybe they're like up here somewhere.
In one of the caves?
Maybe.
Oh god, there's a lot of lava here.
Wheesh!
Barely made it.
Nice.
Uh, have I tried this one?
I have.
In fact, hold on, there is a chest down here I never looted to the left.
I'm gonna try and get that now.
300 Hellbat.
Whoa!
Oh no, I'm burning.
Am I?
I am.
Yeah.
I'm indeed burning alive right now.
There's no doubt about it.
Okay.
Oh, there's something over there.
A trigger.
Definitely want to try that.
All right.
Whoopsie!
That's annoying.
Come back.
Maybe they're somewhere up here.
I think I like this weapon more, actually.
The Crystal Storm?
It's really growing on me.
I like it a lot.
What is that?
Oh wait, it was an enemy.
Are we still in the underworld right now, technically?
Oh wait, I see something.
This is... oh wait, that's a bastard to get to.
I don't want to do that, actually.
There's going to be lava everywhere.
That ain't good.
Oh, who's that?
Skeleton Archer.
Purified!
Yep.
He didn't like that.
Just light up the area a bit here.
Ash block.
Skeleton?
Oh, he dies.
That burns me!
Wait a minute.
I
think this is what works here.
Ah, look at this.
I'm immune to these blocks now.
That's the same type of block where the meteor hit.
Man, I am not seeing anyone.
I am looking.
Scanning every pixel with my eyes.
Maybe it'll be more obvious than I think.
So maybe I just go a little faster.
You know, like, that guy was obvious because he's moving around and stuff.
Ah, look at this.
Now that I will take.
The dainum.
Dude, I am mining so slow.
I need to use this.
Is that really 25%?
That feels like 70% extra.
Am I crazy?
Holy crap.
Oh my god, there's another one.
Alright, back we go.
Probably he wouldn't be down here near the lava, is what I'm thinking.
Because that's kind of bad.
That's a bad spot to be in.
So I'm thinking in one of these caves.
That would make... Oh, there's a chest over there.
Oh, another one of these.
I'll be taking that, thank you.
Get me in here!
Depth meter, dart trap, tin ore.
Ow!
Oh, fuck!
Fuck these chests.
I hate them.
I need that danger sense potion.
I need that danger sense, dude.
Alright, stack things up, delete that.
I'm going to try and ask Marty about this turtle shell.
Hey Marty, you up for a bit of storytelling?
Zoom in on that.
What can I make?
Turtle scale male?
Holy shit!
Enemies are more likely to target you?
Dude!
Oh wait, I need this stuff.
Oh, wait, I remember this now.
Chlorified, I found some of this, but I couldn't mine it.
I forgot what the reason was.
Why couldn't I mine it?
Can I mine it now?
Can mine adamantite and titanium?
Can I make a titanium...
pocket mirror?
Tell me about that.
Oh!
Reflective shades!
Blindfold.
Where do I get that?
Alright, well, we can use it for something.
That's the underlying message here.
Alright, do we have any obsidian potions in our repository?
There's a werewolf knocking on the door.
Well, well, well.
I'm going to pee on you.
Haha!
Fuck you.
Where'd they come from?
Is it a full moon or something?
Titanium barrier.
Oh yeah, right, that's actually what this does.
Yeah, that is what that does.
Now, let's put some stuff in.
Material.
In.
I almost control clicked again, but I caught myself just in time.
This one...
Put it in armor, I guess.
Why not?
Sir, we're closed.
Hoo hoo!
Let's put our money in.
Sort.
And then check for potions.
A gold bunny!
Hap!
You're mine.
A squirrel!
Hap!
You're mine.
Okay, potion?
Danger sense.
Danger...
Ah, I don't have it.
I have to do the thing again.
Gotta go to Marty.
Ask him about the potion.
Okay, I'm gonna pinpoint the danger sense before I even...
See, where is it?
It is... there.
Fuck!
Yeah!
Okay, Shiverthorn and Cobweb.
I got that stuff.
The old Shiverthorn and the old Cobweb.
I have it.
Both of it.
Missionable material.
Cobweb, I have a lot of stuff.
Take all except one.
Shiverthorn?
I've got a cobble.
Better than nothing.
Oh, we stay here in the craft.
Make... that stuff.
Yeah, and I got an extra look from the chance of getting extra potions or not using potion ingredients.
Put the water in.
Um... what is the... Bonnie again?
What could I do with the Bonnie?
Wait.
A golden delight.
Major improvements to all stats.
In fact, I'm gonna make that not eat it.
48 minutes of amazing stat increases.
That actually... I don't know what the fuck... what kind of stats are being increased.
Can I see that somehow?
I can feel it actually.
Am I running faster?
I think I'm definitely running faster with those stat increases.
Maybe it's like all stats.
You know, life regeneration.
Uh... speed... armor?
Maybe.
Oh.
Wait.
To all stats and increase life regeneration.
Okay, yeah, but what are all the... what are the stats?
What's stats?
Tell me specifically what's stats.
I guess like damage, critical strike, defense, everything?
Like everything.
It's gotta be everything.
So in other words, having a nice meal is kind of a big deal.
You know?
Dude, I'm so fast right now with this fleeting, major luminescence.
And there's a burger.
That's gonna be my next meal.
In approximately 47 minutes.
Uh, I wanna go back down.
I'm not done.
I keep forgetting I have this.
Hop, hop, hop, hop, hop.
No.
Ah!
I think it's faster than the railway.
But it's less convenient.
Yeah, look, it doesn't go any further than this.
Living wood stops it.
Living wood is the enemy of Crimson.
Which makes sense, I guess.
Like, logically.
When it comes to fantasy, it's always that.
You know, like...
We have the orcs, who wants to burn down the forest.
And then we have the walkers, the tree ants, the ants.
You know, all that stuff.
Wait, did I cross the... I crossed.
Hot Fadam.
Not to be confused with the town of Rotterdam.
Or the streamer Rotterdam.
Rotterdam 08, for those.
I wanna know more.
Okay, we gotta find this dude now.
And before we do, danger sense.
We're not gonna fall in that same trap.
I forgot to make obsidian.
Potion.
I forgot it.
I did.
It just went out of my mind.
But that's okay, because I feel like we're gonna find this dude now.
Instead of going left, let's go right.
Uh, sir?
Oh, attack speed increase as well.
Dude, I need to find some golden squirrels.
That is incredible!
What an increase!
I've been sleeping on the food.
I just think I haven't noticed, because I've been using the miners that increases.
The major one is literally major.
How about that?
Shit makes sense.
Still wanna know exactly... Oh, look at this.
Two, three, three, six, underworld.
Wait.
Dude!
Why am I getting that stat?
Am I wearing something that... tells me that?
Am I holding something that tells me that?
I have no clue, man.
Why am I getting that statistic?
Dude, my damage is increased as well.
This feels so much better.
Am I crazy?
Torch it, soul!
Where are thou?
I have come to purify you.
Could I be looking down here at all?
No.
I'm not sure.
This is lava, man.
I still think he's gonna be in the house, if anything.
It's gotta be in here, right?
Either that or in one of these caves.
Or maybe it doesn't matter, it's just anywhere in this biome, probably.
Man, look at all the ore up here.
Oh, it's this... it's this biome.
Uh, what was that?
Okay.
Are you down here?
Sir?
Nope.
Oh my god, was I burning?
I didn't even pay attention.
Fuck.
God damn it.
Ah, well.
That's okay, because I'm gonna be doing something now.
What's happening now, it's raining.
Oh, you know what I wanna try?
I wanna try and go to the snow area during rain.
That's a storm then, right?
Let's see if something new happens now.
Or actually, you know, let's check that out first, and then we go to all the other biomes as well.
I wanna see if the weather affects those as well.
I wanna try the jungle.
And the ocean, actually.
Look at this, it's raining blood in this biome.
Come on now.
Okay.
Yeah, look at this.
Oh, but wasn't it something about being there during the night?
What time is it right now?
It's not night, is it?
Maybe I'll try digging down a bit here during the night.
I mean, during the storm.
Okay, then again, the storm doesn't really do anything down here.
Like here, there's a storm.
Look how the background changes.
Umbrella slime.
So cute.
Like, there's so much shit on the screen, I can't even see my particles, like my attacks.
It's very hard.
My god, the weather is terrible.
What if I fish during a storm?
Do I have bait?
I do have bait, nice.
I have the master bait.
This is fine.
Man, come on, where's the storm bass?
Where's the storm cod?
Frost minnow.
I think I've had that before.
Not in real life, but, you know, I found it in here before.
Come on, a frozen crate, maybe a storm crate.
Let's see it.
Man, the thing is breaking all the time.
Look at the water, now it's red, now it's blue.
Now it's red, now it's blue.
Am I technically in a crimson biome when I'm here?
Frozen crimson?
Is that what's going on here?
Mithril crate.
Honder potion, not bad, let me drink that.
Uh, who's shooting?
Ice golem.
Hey, you like pee?
Imma fuck you up, dude.
What do you think of that?
I'm relieving myself on you.
Oh, I don't have any more mana.
Let's chill for a second.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Pee.
This is better.
Oh my god.
Kill him.
Oh my, are you kidding me?
Damn.
Did he drop anything good?
Frost core.
I'm gonna go back for that.
My god, man.
This armor sucks.
It doesn't fucking repel anything.
I feel like I'm just as glass-canony as ever.
Like, it's insane.
At least I see where it dies.
It's not far away.
Joe!
A slime.
I was kind of hoping for a boss to spawn here or something.
Something I could kill.
Wait, what's this?
Oliver's top knot was carved off by debris.
When did that happen?
I have no memory of that.
Anyway, I wasn't done fishing.
Get it.
Please get away from me.
I'm just trying to have a very nice, relaxing fishing session here in this storm.
Oh, again?
These enemies are insane!
Oh, I can arc it!
Am I hitting him?
Oh, wait, I'm not actually hitting anything.
I'm kind of trying to... oh, my god, I'm dying.
I need to find a better way of dealing with this guy.
I am slow AF.
He's very slow, though.
That's kind of something I can take advantage of.
Um, in fact, let's...
Eat the burger.
Major improvements.
There, get Pete on, and then I use the angled attack here.
Something... Wow, he hits me?
What a bastard!
I need to angle this better.
Let me get rid of this.
How did I deal with that guy so easily before?
Oh,
he's just out of reach.
I mean, I am killing him slowly.
Automana.
Give me those stars.
Heal up.
Okay, where'd he go?
We're back in the storm now.
Is he over here?
Ow!
Fucking slimes!
Are suddenly everywhere.
Where did the guy go?
Are we soon, Knight?
Where did he go, dude?
Maybe he disappeared.
Like, where could he have gone, right?
Alright, I'm gonna keep fishing.
I'm gonna do what I came here for.
Actually, I don't know why I came here.
But this was part of it.
Fishing is always good.
A goldfish?
Oh, there he is!
He's back to full health.
And he's killing me.
Oh my god!
Oh, Jesus Christ!
What the fuck?
Dude, the combat in this game is something else, I tell ya.
Did I drop any money?
Actually, you know what?
New plan, new plan.
I'm gonna go try and check the other biomes while it's raining.
That was my initial plan here, I remember now.
I wanna see if something special happens in the jungle.
And the ocean as well.
Utilizing my speed dinosaur here.
Speedosaur?
Oops.
Yep.
Kinda nice that I can knock them.
Okay, how's it hanging here during the rain?
It's still blood.
Wait, what the...
Ha!
I was kind of expecting this to be some kind of rainbow rain.
Let's try the jungle.
Ah!
It's normal rain now, at least.
Okay.
Anything special happening in the jungle?
Not sure.
Let's try the ocean while it rains.
Giant tortoise.
Thank you.
Okay.
What's that?
Giant flying fox?
Yeah!
What the fuck?
I was like, did I read that right?
I sure did.
This looks like some kind of firework, doesn't it?
Imagine a firework in real life that when it explodes, it's just urine everywhere.
Blows into a massive yellow explosion and just urine falls from the sky.
That'd be terrible.
What a terrible firework that would be.
I wouldn't buy it.
Would you buy it?
Okay, the jungle is kind of meh.
Let me kill this guy.
What did I just do?
That was not my intention, but I'm fine.
So many enemies here.
Another tortoise.
I have no more mana.
I feel like I should have a melee weapon for when I don't have mana.
Oh, I'm stuck!
Thank you.
Okay, let's just leave.
I have no mana for this.
I actually do have mana, I just looked.
But I don't care.
Where's my depth meter?
What is giving me this information?
Where the fuck is it?
I can't see it.
This is incredible.
I must be blind.
I cannot fucking see it.
How am I getting this information?
What?
Okay, does it rain in the...
Bahamas?
I was about to say no.
Let's see here.
Let me quickly do a...
water wa...
No.
You know what?
Okay, there's nothing here.
Let's try this.
Maybe the place the teleportation potion takes you is a special place.
Maybe it puts you near a point of interest, so to speak.
Let's see if we can't find a tortured soul somewhere close by.
Oh boy, this is not like a jungle area, actually.
We are in the underworld, sort of.
What am I taking damage from?
Oh, it's fucking lava.
And then this thing, shooting projectiles you cannot possibly see.
Like, look at that!
Fuck you.
I hate those guys so much.
Another tortoise.
Okay, I'm gonna do a quick...
Check down here again for this goddamn...
Oh, I almost died.
For the tortured soul.
If I can't find it, I'm gonna go back to the guide and figure out what the next step is in there.
In this game.
Maybe I misunderstood what he said, I have to go back and reread.
That's a moon glow, isn't it?
I actually need that.
Oh, I'm walking into fire like an idiot.
I'm actually dying.
Oh, kill this guy!
Jungle creeper!
I hate these enemies so much!
Fuck's sake!
These right here...
They remind me of a similar enemy in...
Ah, what's it called?
Hollow Knight.
The single most annoying and difficult enemy in the entire game.
And it's similar looking.
And it's pissing me off.
That projectile there can go fuck itself.
That is some bullshit.
Okay, I'm gonna... I don't even know where it died because I used a teleportation potion.
You know what?
We're chaotic.
We're doing it again.
I'm not intending to go back there.
Where's my other teleportation potion?
Did I only have one?
Maybe I did.
Yeah, fucking rip.
Oh man, where did I die?
I died all the way over there.
Fuck.
That's so far away.
So I have a better idea.
We're gonna be utilizing the...
the pylon network here.
High speed travel.
And we go to here.
And we quickly check the inventory of these people.
You sell all kinds of bullshit.
You sell...
I don't even know.
Stuff I don't want or need.
And mimic!
I wanna kill it.
Hey, bitch!
Ah, you're so dumb.
You having fun down there?
Got it, I think.
Dual hook.
Ah, nice.
I think I found one of those before.
Ah!
Oh, that's the strategy for catching those.
What the fuck?
Mid-air collision!
Where's the air traffic control?
You know what?
Let's go in here.
Angry trapper.
Fuck this guy.
Got him.
Let me pee on you.
I wanna kill more enemies.
I wanna get into...
Oh, no, not these!
I'm about to die now.
And they're also poisoning at the same time.
Can it get any worse?
Okay, there we go.
And now...
Oh, my God.
I literally cannot see the projectile!
I have no idea...
Fuck this.
I'm not fighting these guys.
Nope.
Oh, God.
Leave!
Heal.
We gotta stay here a bit.
Arapaima.
Ah!
This area looks a little intriguing.
Please kill it.
There we go.
I'm almost dead here.
I'm not feeling the 25% cooldown reduction on the healing potion.
I'm really not.
Still feels like forever.
That's like the unit of time that I like to measure things with.
This is at least three forevers.
Maybe it's two and a half forevers after that buff, but...
It's still forever.
That's the point here.
Ah!
It caught me in a web!
You saw that?
I've never seen that.
Alright, you got me.
Good move.
Goddamn.
Ah.
I can't wait till I figure out a good armor set here.
Oh, yeah, frost core.
Let me try that.
Now that I'm back.
Yo, Jamie.
Tell me about the frost core.
Frost breastplate.
Melee and ranged.
Wait.
Ranged critical strike.
Melee and what?
What's the difference?
Oh, it's just the...
Okay, I see.
It's the ingredient difference.
It's the same item.
I want to make the cool whip.
I may actually have this.
Soul of night, soul of light.
I think I have that.
What is happening down here?
Take it outside, people.
Oh!
It's you making that noise.
Wow.
I see.
Soul of...
Whatever.
I have it somewhere.
God damn it, I don't have enough.
I need eight soul of light and eight soul of night.
I need three more.
I can get that.
In fact, let's try and do that.
I want to try the cool whip.
The cool whip sounds cool.
And it's also something you put on a sandwich, right?
I've actually never tried cool whip.
I know it's an American thing.
There's that commercial, right?
Cool whip, that, that, that.
Or something.
That's all I remember.
Maybe I don't.
Maybe I just made that up.
You'll never know.
Yeah.
It's here.
Right?
It's Crimson.
Let me go down here.
Aha!
My world is blessed.
It's so blessed.
You don't even know.
Blessed 420.
What is that sound?
Oh, it's the Wraith.
Will you stop breathing through your mouth?
These guys right here?
Yeah.
My worst nightmare.
Yeah, you like that?
Oh, God.
Let's just get some mana first.
These drop Soul of Night, right?
Honestly, I don't quite remember.
It's been a while.
I'll find out anytime soon here, though.
Or very soon.
I mean.
Not yet.
I'm in a very precarious spot here.
Not good for the health.
How did you get in there?
What's that?
Oh, a blindfold!
I needed that!
Cool!
I can actually make something now.
I have both ingredients for that.
Soul of Night!
There we go!
Let's just catch a bit more of that.
Okay.
I wonder...
Do these guys also drop it, or what?
Hublight?
Gladius.
Are you not entertained?
This guy drops it, though.
The floaty grows.
Oh, this is an annoying position to be in.
Come here!
What the fuck is that?
I guess it's a corpse, but I don't know what that's supposed to look like.
That, to me, looks like...
I don't know, a very hairy eye.
Link groups.
That giant fun guy.
Nah, I don't think it's here.
I need to go back.
Soul of Night, here I come.
Oh, I made that torch, I think.
Also, I want to try and find some of that chlorophyte.
And figure out how to mine it.
I'm a douche.
What is that right there?
Looks like a battery.
Gladiator helmet.
Mining shirt.
What?!
That doesn't work here, though.
I need to equip it there for it to work.
That's actually pretty awesome.
In combination with my...
whatever, ancient chisel.
You know?
It would be quite nice.
Ah, at least these guys drop it, too.
Soul of Night.
How many do I have?
I need one more.
Hey!
Yeah, Soul of Night!
Feels good, man.
Maybe I can get just a bit more, maybe.
I mean, you need it for so many things.
Pee on them!
Oh, it's totally... like, the pee is unreal.
It's so good.
More Soul of Night.
This is the spot to farm it.
It's the spot.
I kinda wanna drain.
Oh, no.
There it is, look.
Let's not mess with that.
Let's not do that.
What's up, people?
I bring gifts.
And when I say gifts, I mean pee and poo.
Actually, only pee.
Kill it.
Nice.
Ouch!
Uh-oh, I'm in a bad spot, I'm in a bad spot.
I don't know what the fuck is going on.
I can't see shit.
There's so many particles.
Monster meat.
Summons?
A small pig man.
Okay.
Is it like a follower, just like the other ones?
Let's try it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Fuck!
Are we good?
Is it... that one?
Oh, yeah, a little pig man.
Sup, pig man?
Uh, nothing down there.
Ah, a chest!
Wait, why am I not just going down like...
Fucking hell, I can't see the enemies!
I think this guy just spawned in front of me.
Like, how did he get in there?
I cleared this place already.
For fuck's sake, man.
God damn it.
Where'd I die?
Okay, it's not too bad.
Let's go.
What's the best way down?
Honestly, probably this.
Verticalius Maximus, and then take a right.
At the appropriate time.
Uh-oh, go this way instead.
What's that sound?
Blood mummy?
Have I killed that before?
No, no, you heard it?
It was to the left.
Dark shard.
Hey you!
Let's try and listen now.
Come on.
Make a sound.
There.
You hear it?
It's somewhere down below, I think.
Fuck off.
Yeah, it's right here.
Maybe if I kill enough of these, something will happen.
Or maybe I just dig.
But the thing is, it's kind of hard to dig with these guys.
Everywhere.
Equip that.
Light.
Let's go.
Block it off.
Oh, I can't!
Fuck me.
Oh, I'm silenced!
Fuck!
Goddamn!
Pigman, help me!
I'm so dead.
There's a huge monster somewhere here.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Wow.
Come on, I need to heal.
Do I have anything I can block with?
Thank the Lord.
Heal?
We're fine, right?
There's something down here.
Oh!
Ouch.
Where are you?
Where's it coming from?
Make a sound.
Why does this look like that?
The hell?
I'm not hearing the growling anymore.
It's to the right.
It's...
What?!
It's right here!
Where?!
Is it the enemies making the sound?!
There's no way!
It sounds way too loud!
It's got to be a boss or something!
I mean, when I kill these, the sound...
Yeah, it's got to be these.
By the way, these guys don't drop Soul of Night while I'm here.
It's only underground.
Have you noticed?
That's kind of interesting.
Wait a minute.
Soul of Night.
Are we literally talking about no light?
If I remove this...
If I remove torches...
No way, right?
Hold on, let me remove this torch as well.
I'm going to remove everything here.
I'm testing.
Nah, I think it's underground.
Maybe at a certain depth.
You know, that's when things happen.
Megaphone!
Where?
There.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Let's go home.
Uh, sort.
Now it's time to ask Mikey.
Yo, Mikey!
Tell me about...
I know this already.
Wait a minute.
Didn't I find something new?
Anyway, I can craft things now.
Remind me of the materials.
Wait a minute.
Is that how I got this?
No way, I wouldn't have used this on that.
Mechanical worm...
Summons the destroyer.
That doesn't sound pleasant to me.
Decay chamber...
and flesh clo... yeah.
Bro, what is happening here?
People are dying!
Close the door!
Wait, there's actually a hole in my...
I need to fix that.
I don't have any wood.
Fuck!
It's in my chest.
Dude, quickly remind me here of...
this.
Stop.
Cool web, cool web!
Eight, eight!
Frost!
Fucking leave me alone.
Uh, okay.
Close this door.
My god, the weather is just crazy!
It's been raining forever!
Possessed armor banner.
Huh.
Get rid of it.
I don't want it.
Vanity?
I have so many red hats!
We gotta sell some of them.
Do I have duplicates?
Seems good.
Okay, now.
Miscellaneous.
Uh, no materials.
Grab...
light...
night...
I need only eight.
And a frost core.
And then I can make it, apparently.
Somewhere here.
There.
Cool web!
Let me have some of that cool web.
Your summons will focus struck enemies.
That's good, though.
Wait, six summon tag damage?
Uh...
Huh?
What?
Why does it say summon damage?
What does that mean?
How is this not a melee weapon?
Oh!
It's a melee weapon that...
spawns...
What?
Is that what's happening?
What the...
Cool web!
Oh, yeah.
I mean, this is a great AOE, though.
Like...
If it hits everything in the...
Bro, this is a sick weapon?
And the reason I say that is, I don't even have my melee stuff on.
Whoa, uh...
What if I went all melee?
No, wait, but...
Summon damage?
I don't understand this.
Does that mean I do 48, or does my summon do 48?
That's so confusing.
No, I definitely do, like, 48.
Look.
52, 47, that's my damage.
Why am I so slow?
Oh, I had a debuff.
But then I apply some kind of frost effect to it.
Strike enemies to summon a friendly snowflake, yeah.
Okay.
This is actually pretty sick.
Do I have any melee items?
Like, so I have, for example, I have this, which is useless for me right now.
I have that, which is useless for me right now, you know.
I can replace all of these, potentially.
With amazing items.
Melee stuff.
Maybe I want to shield them, actually.
If I'm going melee...
Why do I have so many of these?
Sell some of this shit.
And that one.
There was something else I could craft.
Before I forget.
It was...
I think... God, I don't remember.
Which one was it?
Let's just sell real quick.
Keep a clean inventory here.
Also, what if I use this?
Can I then make two snowflakes?
I'm sorry, Star.
I thought I just hit her for, like, a bunch of damage.
Alright, you sell me...
No.
Take a bunch of these.
Edgar has arrived.
Fuck the rain hat.
That one.
Sell that one, these ones, and...
All these shields.
The helmet.
That one.
Nice.
This looks clean.
Seaweed.
I think I prefer my turtle.
I mean, you know what?
The pigman is actually kind of cool.
Let's keep the pigman.
Pigman rocks.
Alright.
So, I needed to combine this with something else.
Is it in here, I wonder?
What do I have in here?
Oh, wait a minute!
I have a blindfold in here.
What?
Wait.
No way!
Things in your void bag...
apparently...
also work!
Oh god, am I really gonna have to experiment with all the accessories to check which ones do not need to be equipped?
Which ones can go in the void bag?
What the fuck, man?
What?
What are these systems?
There's no way.
And there's the megaphone I found.
It's in here now.
Delete that.
Put that there.
Geyser can be deleted.
Delete that.
Keep this in here, I guess.
What tells the time right now?
Where's my watch?
Is it in here?
How am I telling the time?
Fucking understand what's giving me this now.
In any case, I can sell that.
And I can test these with Jimmy.
Where is he?
Ralph!
Remind me about this.
Pocket mirror.
There it is.
That's the one I needed.
Let's grab it.
Pocket mirror.
What?
What's happening?
I leave the house for one second.
Fucking close the doors, people.
Maybe that was me.
I'm sorry.
Maybe I left the door open.
That was probably me.
Won't happen again.
Where's that thing?
Did I put it in here?
Where did I put it?
This God forsaken thing.
I'm losing my mind.
Is it in here?
It's not.
Where did I put that fucking mirror?
Did I accidentally put it in a random ass chest somewhere?
I did.
I thought this was...
Oh my God.
I wish I could search for items.
Okay, finally I got it.
Let's combine them.
Jesus.
And I think I can do that right here.
Reflective shades, dude.
There it is.
Finally.
Let's try and give that to Edgar.
Look at it.
Here we go.
Another piece of the puzzle.
I have these now.
I have that.
I think I have the plan?
I have that?
I don't have that.
That's like the only thing I need.
But wait, what about the megaphone?
Alright, that's how I made this to begin with.
I did have a memory of having this before.
Or having had that before.
There's nothing else I can use this for, right?
No.
So I guess I can sell this.
Sold.
Why not?
Okay.
God, Jimmy, I wish you could come with me and just stand next to these boxes over here.
Like I assigned you to.
Dalamar has arrived.
I mean, people just come and go in these parts.
They freaking die left and right.
It's not looking good.
Hello?
It's a gnome.
That's why you leave the doors closed.
Alright, next up, click this button.
Magic things happen.
Oars and doors.
Put the oars in.
And...
What now?
I need guidance here.
Actually, let me talk to this guy.
You sell anything?
See, now they can't come in.
That's why you close the doors.
Marty, help.
I've heard of glowing mushrooms growing big enough on the surface to gain sentience.
Really?
Slash doubt.
I've been everywhere.
But I guess I can go everywhere again to check.
A lot of people have moved in lately, haven't they?
Party girls.
Mhm.
Yup.
Make sure to smash any crimson altar you can find.
Something good is bound to happen if you do.
Yeah, I've been doing it, dude.
I've been doing it.
Souls can sometimes be gathered from fallen creatures in places of extreme light or dark.
Okay, I don't think this means literally.
It means light and dark as in dark forces and light forces.
You know, the good and evil.
So, crimson down below.
Good.
Normally, I try to teach you...
Yeah, shut up.
When the moon goes...
Shut up.
You can remove people from their home.
I wish I could remove you.
You hear me?
Jeremy.
Have you seen the wyvern soaring high up in the clouds?
If only I could fly like that.
Yeah.
Well, you can't.
Try combining a hell forge with some titanium ore.
I bet you could make some really powerful stuff with that.
I think I did that already.
And powerful?
I don't know about that, dude.
It kind of sucks.
The titanium armor here?
Nope.
I hear there's a woman out there.
Me too.
There's women everywhere.
Stylist.
Tell me where he is.
Down in the underworld sure looks familiar.
On him.
Wait.
Familiar?
Wait a minute.
Hold your horses.
Oh shit.
I have an idea here.
I have an idea.
Get rid of this stuff.
I hate these fucking enemies everywhere.
I swear to god, dude.
Like, you can't go four seconds.
You can barely check your inventory when you're not at home, you know?
I'm gonna go all the way down now.
So remember I had the idea of throwing the doll into the shimmer.
Didn't do anything.
Because I thought, hey, I'ma purify you, I'ma clean you, you know?
I'ma cleanse you of this curse.
I'm gonna do something similar now.
But with purification powder.
Hold on, maybe you don't need to be down there.
Hold on, let me only throw one.
Fuck!
Wait a minute.
Get whipped!
Cool whip!
This is a pretty good weapon, dude.
And it's not even optimized, the stuff I have for it.
Please leave me alone for two seconds!
There?
And then, where's my...
Where's my powder?
Oh, it's there now.
God damn it.
Okay, quick!
Before the enemies come!
There?
Uh, there?
Wait, did I accidentally walk into it before?
Wait a minute, I gotta try that once more.
There?
Hmm.
Maybe I need to be in the underworld.
Look at the guy holding a...
That's funny.
It's like, what is this girl name that cleans houses?
Comes down the chimney.
Mary Poppins, right?
It's like Mary Pickens.
The third.
There's gold there, but I don't want it.
Okay.
No, okay.
I thought for a second this maybe would be the tortured soul.
Think about it.
Who is the most tortured person in this game?
It's Frank.
It's the guide.
Right?
He is so tortured, he dies every fucking three minutes.
You feel vibrations from deep below.
Great.
I love vibrations.
Uh, I'll see what that means in a second here, I guess.
But first, we shall find the tortured soul.
I am committed now.
What is that?
Lost Hopes of Man.
I have no idea what that means.
No idea what that means.
Let me put on this also, because I'm in the underworld.
Let me put on that instead of that.
Also, get out of here.
I kind of want to cool-wave it up, you know?
Actually, do I?
Let me go back to magic for a second.
Uh, there.
I think this is better than this.
Actually, I'm not sure.
Hmm.
I think I'm about to face a boss down here now.
Come on.
Where's the vibrations?
Vibrazione?
Okay.
Where are Vibrazione?
Soul... no, nice.
Bro, the whip is insane!
Look at how good it is!
Also, cool whip sounds like the perfect place or the weapon to use while you're down here, right?
Everything is very hot and steamy.
tortured soul.
Hmm.
It's really good against these small enemies everywhere.
That's really the...
I have a feeling that my favorite weapon in this game is going to be one of those where I can just...
cleanse an AOE area, you know?
Like, just get rid of a bunch of small annoying fucks.
Oh, God.
Can't believe it hit me.
Oh, look!
You know what?
Let's make it fall.
I don't care.
Do it!
Oh, wait.
Did I pick it up?
I guess I did.
I also got a heal anyway.
Let's go to the left here and try and summon this guy now.
Apparently, these vibrations didn't do shit.
Vibrations below you.
Wait a minute.
Does this go through?
No way.
Wait a minute.
Can you change position?
Oh, my God!
I keep getting hit by the lava.
You definitely need obsidian potion down here.
Now I know why I'm so slow.
I don't have my...
Oh, my God.
I'm dying here.
Get out of here.
Yeah, this ain't good.
I need to make obsidian potions right fucking now.
I've had it.
I have had it.
I even have one, but I need one here at least.
Okay, bottled water, and then I need some obsidian, I guess.
That makes sense.
Obsidian.
Take everything but one.
And then I have to go remind myself.
Gotta ask Charles.
What do I actually need to make it?
Fire blossom, water leaf.
Gotcha.
Fire blossom.
I have plenty.
Leave one.
Oh, nice.
I have plenty of this as well.
That is beautiful.
Thank God.
Fifteen.
I just got so relieved.
All right.
What's next?
Can I do anything with my remaining soul of night?
Obsidian brick.
Get rid of that.
Um, click this button.
The daybloom goes in here.
Kinda want to find more dayblooms.
Oh yeah, let me sell these before I forget.
Where are thou?
I will sell to you this time.
These three?
I need to make more food that gives me major improvements to all stats.
That is a banger when you have that.
But...
There's like no way of knowing which fucking recipe that is.
Unless you literally remember.
So, I don't know.
Maybe some kind of fish.
You know?
Uh, maybe I have a sick fish.
You know what?
Let's try this armored cave fish.
I don't remember ever trying that.
Let's try some different ones.
Frost minnow.
Oh, and also one of each, please.
Goes back.
So it don't cause a...
Mayhem.
Princess fish.
Uh, specular.
That is bait.
So is that.
That goes in the fishing one.
There you go.
Oh wait.
I just put it back where I took it.
That's right, I did combine those, I remember now.
Uh, alright, Dave.
What about the damsel fish?
Medium improvements and calming potion.
I think I'm gonna need to make some calming potions.
Oh, I need daybloom, I don't have that.
I only have one.
Dang it all.
What about this?
Medium improvements, you know what?
That's not...
Hello?
The fucking crimson is at our doorstep here.
Hold on, what's the status on that anyway?
I mean, it's not going any further.
But it's kind of annoying that it's right here now.
Because it spawns these enemies and they fly into my home.
Close the door.
Alright.
Let's continue.
Frost minnow.
It reduces damage from cold sources.
Huh.
Really?
Cold sources, huh?
Maybe I should drink this when I fight a frost boss.
Or something like that.
Wait, Captain Bullywort?
Are you an enemy or are you...
real?
Yar, funny should be mentioned in parrots because, um, what we're talking about.
I don't remember.
Wait, what?
What?
A sail?
Alright.
Really, a cannon?
I gotta try this.
Wait a minute.
Gotta put it up here, of course.
No, turn it around.
The other way!
Alright, whatever.
Apparently this doesn't work anymore when you turn left or right.
I'm building!
Fuck off.
There.
Alright!
300 damage, huh?
I mean, that's not bad, but it's kind of hard to aim.
You know what the great thing about the cool whip is?
I could go with magic style, right?
With magic items and all that.
And then when I'm low on mana, I cool whip.
I whip out the cool.
That's a great way to start doing some damage.
While I'm low on mana, because it's a great item.
It's really good.
Super good for utility.
Just clearing out these small annoying enemies.
So I think I'm gonna keep going the way I was going with my magic stuff.
And then just occasionally whip out the whip, you know?
That's the plan.
Okay.
What else do I wanna do?
Did I try the princess?
I don't think I did.
Princess.
Loft potion and seafood dinner.
I mean, medium improvements is also nice.
I was hoping...
Oh, Ella is throwing items.
She's throwing a wen... a wrench.
If you can dodge a wrench, you can dodge a ball.
Oh, it's Stein.
The slime.
I wonder if all their names rhyme with slime.
Okay.
Goes in.
And that's why we leave one behind.
Bottled water.
Go back in here.
I wanna try this again.
Go.
Hey.
Cool.
Looks like a cool place.
Snowflinks!
Get whipped!
Flinks fur!
That's where I got all that.
Live crystal, nice.
What was this?
Nice.
This is kind of a cool looking biome, though.
Oh, wait, I'm confused.
Man, the confused debuff is...
Well, it's living up to the name, let me tell you.
What happens?
Oh, yeah, right.
We make obsidian like this.
I just wanna dig here.
Probably my favorite thing in this game is just exploring caves.
But there's actually...
Oh!
There's a bunch of gold on the ground.
There's the temple still.
That I don't know how to get into.
I just remembered.
Here.
I should try and go back soon.
Maybe something changed now that I unleashed all this stuff on the world.
There we go.
Oh, wait, now I'm going down to where I already was earlier.
I wanna stay up here in the frost.
I feel like that could be some cool items there.
In fact, let me try and fish here.
Maybe this is not enough water.
Nah, it's gotta be a bit more.
Actually, why am I so slow?
Oh!
I'm constantly chilled.
I guess because I go in the water.
Doesn't that kind of look like an animal with a head?
Burning eyes?
Look at that.
Looks like a leaping...
...leopard.
I wonder if that's where they get their name from.
Leopards, because they leap?
It's not quite the same, but you know.
Shower thought there.
Where am I going?
Um...
Yeah, sure.
Don't I have one of those nice potions I can use?
Nah, I was looking for the treasure potion.
Unfortunately, it's not there.
Oh, that's titanium!
Didn't even notice.
Actually, I just...
I wonder if you can even reach credits in this game.
I don't know how that would work.
My guess is you defeat one... some last boss or something.
And then the credits are there.
Vikings?
Ice elements.
And ice tortoise!
Oh, God.
Man, the whip is great.
I like this song right here.
Give me that.
I feel like I've never really explored this biome.
Wait a minute.
Oh, this is all like... I thought this was a background.
What the hell?
Oh!
What?
Oh, you could just fall like that!
I'm getting so much titanium, and I don't even know what to use it for.
Apparently, it's this great ore that will give you amazing armor, but...
I've yet to see this amazing armor.
So far, all I've seen is mediocre armor.
Actually, it's worse than that.
Give me the unholy arrow.
Man, there's so much titanium here.
Whoops.
Let me go this way.
Or maybe it's one of those things where if you explore the entire map, that's when the game really ends, you know?
It's all about digging in this game.
Digging, digging, digging.
It's got to be a boss thing.
Reaching the credits, right?
I actually hope it's not.
I would rather not kill any bosses, honestly.
I just want to explore these caves.
No bosses, please.
Where's my... Oh, I used all my torches!
Holy shit.
Let's bring out the normal ones, then.
Back to normal torches.
What are you?
An icy merman.
You dropped money.
Everyone has money on them, apparently.
Oh!
Didn't mean to fall through that.
What is that in there?
It's emerald, right.
Look at that!
A shiverthorn just in a single tile, surrounded by ice.
Life always finds a way.
Er...
I want to kill that.
I want a frost shell.
Maybe that's not what they drop.
Speaking of shells, there was something I could make with the tortoise shell, and I got a couple extra.
I gotta try that.
Oops.
It's so slippery here.
Oh, there's gold in there!
Not that I really care too much about gold at this point.
But, you know, when I see it, I'm gonna take it, of course.
I mean...
Sup, icy merman?
Icy elemental?
Wait, I didn't take the gold.
There we go.
Sup, man?
Dude.
It's Friday, dammit.
I just remembered.
The best feeling when you just remember it, after forgetting it.
You know what the best thing is, too, in the weekends?
You said you're a long clock.
Very early.
And then you wake up, and you're like, oh fuck, I gotta go to work and all that, right?
But then, no, you don't!
Because it's weekend!
And you can have that every day!
If you said you're a long clock, really early.
Little life hack for you there.
I swear it works.
What is that?
Oh, I thought it was like a door thingy.
Okay, so we are actually getting quite far down.
We're approaching the underside.
Oh.
Giant bad banner?
Look at this, I have a shit ton of potions.
Where'd I put them?
Oh, don't tell me they went into the...
Wait a minute, what's that?
Hasty philosopher's stone.
Yoink!
That's mine.
25%.
Oh yeah, wait a minute!
This is a material as well!
I have to try that with Jack.
I think I did try it once, but there's no way I remember that.
The combinations here are absurd.
So, maybe we can do some crazy stuff with that.
Get out of here!
Nice.
Oh, this is actually bad.
Just let him die in the lava.
Oh god!
It's me who's dying in the lava.
What are we finding down here?
Look at this, there's ice right next to the lava.
What a weird little contrast here.
What do we have here?
What was that sound?
Was that you making that sound?
Sunflower statue.
Wait a minute, did it go in here?
It did.
Let me check something.
If I now do this...
I thought for a second maybe this would count as a sunflower as well, but just maybe with more range or something.
The statues are a little confusing.
I feel like they work sometimes and other times they don't.
If I even understand them correctly, that's a big if.
I think I do, but...
Probably not.
This area.
Okay, so when it's like purple, it always goes in the void ray.
I have to...
Void ray...
I've been playing so much Starcraft.
It goes into the void bag.
Look how slow I'm damaging them.
But when I pee on them, it's like...
I almost want to say twice as fast.
Maybe 30% quicker.
Also, I've been in this spot a million times.
This is like a very well-known spot to me.
I think.
Or maybe they just look alike.
It's also possible.
What do we have here?
Oopsie.
Archer.
What's that?
Lead.
Of all the ores, lead is actually one of the more useful ones.
Oh, there you are.
I heard you.
Okay.
I'm going to cut back to the right over here and then go down again.
See if I can't find this goddamn soul.
It's got to be somewhere.
I wonder if it's like a randomized thing.
Like every time I go back down to the underworld, there's like a different spot this guy could appear in.
Or if it's like preset from the moment the world was generated or something, you know.
I'm assuming it's the first option there.
Because everything seems a little random like that so far.
Okay, then we go down.
Perfect route.
You die.
Okay, where do I go?
Just down.
Like, is this technically the underworld?
It's like the question, right?
I don't think it is.
Like this?
No.
I think when you see the background with the little cave in the distance, that's the...
Oh, wait a minute.
What does that look like that?
There's a weird texture in the background.
What's up, dudes?
Wait, I have...
No, I was about to say I've been here, but I haven't.
That's scary.
Let's not venture down there.
We make our own path.
Ash block.
Dude, for a second I thought this was the tortured soul, but it's just my pig companion.
Damn you!
Okay.
So I am right now, all the way to the left.
I'm going to systematically check every one of these buildings now.
Because I think, for me, that's probably the most likely place that person would be.
Think about a tortured soul.
Who would torture someone down here?
The inhabitants of this place.
Where do the inhabitants live here, right?
Maybe there's like a little prison chamber or something.
Where the guy is being held.
I'm not seeing anything.
This is a big complex, though.
What about here?
Checking absolutely everything.
Leave him alive.
My guess is it's an NPC that can appear in my town.
When I finally cure him of his torture or rescue him.
No, pure him.
Purify him.
Purification powder.
Come here.
There you go.
Okay, let's check here now.
I also feel like I would have seen this tortured soul before I beat the wall of flesh.
Because I checked all these buildings, remember?
Wait, Titan Potion?
What does that do?
Knockbag increase.
Right.
How about here?
Oh!
Tortured soul!
There it is!
That was right!
All right, get the powder.
P-p-p-p-p-p-powder.
There it is, dude.
He's probably an enemy right now, yeah, he definitely is.
I just came from Isix!
He wanted...
I'm talking to Chester!
Two barrels of molasses plus!
Oh, never mind that, you're here.
Here's your money.
What?
You again?
I just grabbed some of my coin just moments ago, so bugger off and come back later.
What?
The fuck are you talking about?
Did I just get some money or what?
Must everyone open and shut doors so incredibly noisily around here?
I just gave you half a crown five minutes ago.
Scram!
Uh...
Wait, half a crown?
Are you Danish by any chance, Chester?
You again?
Suppose you want more mo- Okay, so he's gonna probably appear in my town.
Right?
Look at that demon.
What's up demon?
Alright, it's time.
We head back.
Alright Chester, show your face.
Yeah!
The tax collector!
Uh-huh.
Tried to get Nissa to pay me with favors once.
Now I have fungus growing in strange places.
Alright dude!
Alright!
What the fuck?
We should cut out the taxes that I've taken from our surplus population- Okay.
Chester's dead.
Fucking hell.
Well, at least I got to extract the money from him before he kicked the old bucket.
That's something.
Alright, cool.
Another member joins the population and now I get to tax people.
This is getting better and better.
Fill up the chests.
By the way, uh...
Isa?
Nissa?
He's talking about Rosalva there.
The Dryad.
Because the Dryad right now is called Nissa.
So yeah.
For those that don't know.
Uh, remove this.
Nobody wants you.
Silt!
Okay.
Alright, Mr. Brock.
Brock the Haven.
What do I do next?
Uh, I've heard of glowing mushrooms growing big enough on the surface to ga- okay.
Let's try and find a glowing mushroom on the surface trying to gain sentience.
I'm looking for that right fucking now.
We're going to the right.
I hate that I can't use this house anymore because of this goddamn crimson.
And I have no idea how to get rid of it.
And purification powder is a joke.
Because that's such a nice house I spent so long building it.
And now it's just crap.
Alright mushroom, show yourself.
Gimme.
I'm too slow.
Put this on.
And eat this.
There we go.
Get that energy.
Hello!
Thank you.
Any mushrooms?
Let's actually check up here too.
Wait, no.
Okay.
Glowing mushrooms.
Glo- wait, no, those are just thingies on the water.
Man, where- there!
No wait, I need to find...
What are these other things that I really need?
It's a flower.
I'll see it when I see it.
Or I'll know it when I see it.
It's a very basic flower.
The most basic of basics.
Mushroom.
Maybe these mushrooms will be moon glow?
Maybe these mushrooms will be easier to see during the night.
They're growing, right?
Or glowing.
What do you give me?
Alright, keep going.
Urine is their weakness.
Oh, mushroom.
What's that?
Not what I thought it was.
Dopesy!
A durpling.
That's a great name.
Let me try and catch that.
Oh, I can't.
Whoa, you came flying there.
There we go.
P on you.
And then we crystal shard you.
Do, do, do, do, do.
Get him.
So many turtles.
Okay, I haven't seen the mushroom yet.
So violent when they break apart.
Another... Wow, they're so close.
Two meteor hits here.
Wait a minute.
No.
Nope.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, shit, we've reached the ocean.
Okay.
Hmm.
Also, what's this about me having more bark?
Can you tell me something about this crimson, dude?
Twenty percent crimson.
It's increasing.
How do I make it go away, Rosalva?
I mean, obviously, purification powder cleanses the evil.
I don't know.
Maybe it's determined by how many good things we're growing in that area or something.
But I can't place these on the ground.
They need to be in, like, planters and stuff.
I could place this sort of stuff.
Wait, potted forest palm.
Potted jungle palm and potted hello palm.
Prevention from accidentally destroying the environment.
Huh.
Is this really exactly what it says?
I need to see this.
I need to understand this.
Because that sounds...
I don't even know why I would want to have that effect.
Well, now it's active.
It should prevent you from...
So, I'm in the inventory now.
I'm destroying the environment.
What does this mean?
Guys, also, it's a material.
While in the inventory.
Huh?
Made this inventory?
I can still destroy the environment.
Do I need to have it in my hands, maybe?
Wait.
No, of course not, because then I can't destroy the environment.
I need my pickaxe.
I have no clue.
No clue.
Uh, magically moves dirt.
Let me try this again.
Uh, this one?
Okay, now I have it equipped now.
Let me find dirt.
Okay.
It does exactly what it says.
Perfect.
It magically moves the dirt.
Okay, that makes sense at least.
But that doesn't help me against the crimson.
I don't know.
I think I need to talk to...
Jeremy.
I mean, he's the only real guide I have.
In this world.
Oh, wait, you're not the guide.
Help me more.
Help, help, help.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, so the old one's army.
But...
That's kind of insane.
We've seen the wyvern soaring high up in the clouds.
Are you talking about the annoying fucking creatures that keep attacking when you're on the island?
Hold on, let me go to Lion Pines again.
Let me actually see what the hell he's talking about.
Um, I need my specialized potion for this.
The ultimate gravitation potion.
Let's get, uh, just one of them.
Yikes, there we go.
Get away from me.
Right.
He should be up here.
Man,
look at this guy living the life.
Look at this!
He has the best view in town.
A cool ass little hut.
With a spinning thingy.
That's awesome.
And he's just up here golfing.
Huh?
You eat what for breakfast?
What are you selling me again?
What is the point?
Let's play some golf.
Golf ball.
Golf tea.
Golf whistle.
Sure.
Let's do this.
What the fuck is the point of this?
There we go.
Oh, that's a harpy.
Okay, so that's not a wyvern.
Uh...
Do we go higher for the wyvern?
Wait, let me keep...
Keep falling into space.
No, it doesn't let me.
I fall down again.
I can't go higher than this!
Alright, let me continue my golf experiment.
Okay.
Oh, please leave me alone while I golf.
So, let me try... let me try this now.
Here.
Golf ball.
There we go.
Wait, equippable?
What?
No way.
Hey, hole in one!
Right into the crimson.
Wow, this is a bouncy-ass ball.
Not bad.
I can hold it.
Oh, I can aim it!
Hey, lion pints!
Check this out.
Wow.
Not bad.
Uh...
Here we go.
Let's try again.
Let me golf at peace.
What is the point of the golfing, though?
I don't understand.
I have to remember.
Terraria is like...
Wow, I actually hit almost the exact same spot again.
That's incredible.
Uh, it's also like a multiplayer game, right?
Maybe this is just what people do.
They just fucking golf.
What?
Oh, I hit a cloud.
My god.
Let me go straight up.
I'm gonna hit the moon.
Don't hit my head.
Wait, can I kill?
Hold on.
Ah!
Man, I was so hoping I could one-shot this harpy with that golf ball.
That would have been glorious.
Shoot the golf balls.
No, okay, it doesn't work.
Would have been funny, though.
I'm actually gonna try and hit this flag now.
Let's see.
Terrible.
Let's try...
Ah!
Fucker.
Oh, I can also do this.
Oh my god, this is so fucking annoying.
Like, what am I... Okay, hold on.
So, whenever I want to do anything in this fucking world, am I supposed to...
Am I supposed to just...
do this every time I want to do anything without getting interrupted?
But I have to golf, so I need to see.
Golf ball, where are you?
Maybe it works.
It does.
Okay.
Go again.
Okay, let's try and put this flag a little further away.
There.
You know what, that's gonna be a little difficult to hit.
What if we...
What if we cheat?
We make...
Wait a minute.
There's no way.
Can I just... Oh my god.
I'm gonna cheat.
We're cheating here.
We're making a funnel.
Wait a minute, is this actually gonna work?
Oh, that's a bit too high.
That's a bit too high as well.
Wow, okay, hold on.
This ain't the spot for it.
Let's put it, uh...
here.
Ah, shit.
Wait a minute.
Hey, wait, what?
Didn't go in?
Bro.
Fuck off.
How did that not...
Maybe nothing happens when it goes in.
That's a holding one.
Come on.
How is that not a perfect shot?
All right.
All right, Lion Pines, I'm done with you.
I'll be moving out again.
Thanks for the golf lesson, man.
Let me put everything back where I found it.
There you go.
Heavy down.
All right.
On to the next.
Let me get rid of all this golfing shit.
I don't think I'll ever do that again.
The dirt rod can also go away.
I don't ever want to do that again.
Return to your last hit golf ball to its previous...
What?
I guess it's for a minigame, you know, when you play on multiplayer servers.
That's what makes sense to me there.
Okay, now I kind of regret not bringing more gravitation potions.
A chicken nogget!
Incredible.
Let's eat it.
Why not?
Just do it.
Okay.
I want to go up to more islands now, see if I can find some wyverns.
But I feel like I've been everywhere already.
But then again, I did unleash new forces on the world.
So maybe they're now suddenly there, you know?
In places they weren't before.
So we need some more of those flying potions.
And I'm talking lots of flying.
Gimme three.
Yoink!
Ha ha!
Wait, can I?
Wait.
Oh, I can't do it on a mount, unfortunately.
That's too bad.
Oh, look at this.
I'm walking upside down on that.
This is so trippy.
Very weird.
Maybe they only appear at night.
Wyvern!
Oh, Wyvern showed thyself to me.
I need to...
What was that?
Just a harpy?
Yeah, just a harpy.
Goddamn harpies.
Goddamn harpies!
Wait.
Oh, this is another island.
Let's see if they're here.
Oh!
There we go.
That's a Wyvern.
Oh my god.
Hold on.
Hold on now.
Oh, look!
I'm peeing on sections of it!
Oh, fuck!
I...
Okay, yeah.
Alright.
I was not ready for that.
That caught me completely off guard.
Holy shit.
Whew!
Okay, now I know where it is.
It's time to pee all along that Wyvern now.
And then slay it.
Feels good, man.
Whoops.
Let's have a dead potion again.
See ya.
What's that?
Oh wait, it's my guy!
I thought it was like someone following me, but it's my little guy following...
Yeah, so I guess he is...
Yo, that's a way to do it!
Oh, you can't mount when you're upside down, huh?
Isn't that interesting?
But you can gain some horizontal speed like that.
Alright, Wyvern!
There it is!
It's back!
Okay, pee.
Dodge.
Let's actually try this now.
Oh, no!
Okay, sure.
We can fight like this!
Come on, now!
Bro, this is...
This is something else.
We're out now!
There it is!
Oh, fuck!
That was a bit funny, though.
Okay, I can definitely kill that, that's no problem.
I'm fucking around a bit too much right now.
I just need to pull myself together here.
And you know what?
I think I may even bring a little statue with me.
Oh, fuck, I lost that statue, didn't I?
I got rid of that.
On accident.
Or did I?
Wait a minute.
Maybe I didn't.
Ah, there it is!
Yeah, I got it.
Alright, let's do a...
Let's have a major improvements.
Those stats here.
The apple pie from scratch.
Sort items, take this here.
And get ready to place it.
And you know what else I wanna do?
Sundial!
Make
it day so I can actually see what the fuck is going on.
And then I want...
Sure, let's take one of these.
Drink that.
Honestly, not much else is something I want.
The rest needs to stay there for sorting purposes.
It is a must.
Also, I didn't start the last battle with full health.
That's something to keep in mind there.
Alright, let's go.
Where is it?
It's over there, okay.
That is such a loud noise.
I'm starting to think it's not actually a boss hiding somewhere.
It's just one of the random ass enemies.
Who for some reason has a very loud sound effect.
Alright, we fly up now.
Heel real quick.
It should be here now.
Statue.
Unless they only appear in the night, actually.
That could actually be the case.
In which case, I guess I'll come back.
Oh, look at that.
I'm walking on the roof.
That's funny.
Dude.
That would be a way to fight the wall of flesh.
You just go upside down and you walk along the roof.
You don't have to worry about the lava.
She's upside down.
That would be kind of cool to try, I guess.
But I mean, I guess it's not an even surface anyway.
The roof, it's like a little, you know, random.
Let me continue, see if I can't find him.
Maybe he just despawned.
For whatever reason.
Look at that rainbow.
We are in Schlaraffenland.
That's what it looks like, at least.
Fly...
Oh, great wyvern of the sky.
Okay, peeing on these guys is actually quite effective.
Like, just the pee.
You don't even need a follow-up, just pee on them.
That's already good enough.
A wyvern.
I wonder if I can pull the wyvern with me down to the surface when I pull it.
This is the most confusing way to fight ever.
What's that?
A toucan.
Don't know how to say that.
Alright, upside down.
Anything in this immediate area?
I think they gotta be next to the islands, right?
Otherwise, it's kinda hard to fight them, I guess.
Yeah, I think it's during the night.
It's gotta be during the night.
We go back in the night.
Wait!
I got solar flight!
No fucking way!
Run!
Look at this!
Allows... wait, what?
Allows flight?
That's useless.
I already have flight and slow fall.
What are you talking about?
This even gives me a super fast running speed.
What's the point?
Allows flight and slow fall.
Press down.
Okay, now we're talking.
What's this?
Shroomite!
Hello?
I guess I find that in the shroom caverns.
Wait, wait, wait, shroomite?
I've never seen that!
The hoverboard, now that is something I'm interested in here.
Hold on, let me see the other ones.
They're all just the same.
Solar flight in a bottle?
None of these are materials either, so there's no real reason to make them.
What the fuck?
Solar flight, feather, solar flight.
Yeah, doesn't make any sense.
Why would I ever do that?
I mean, okay, maybe if you didn't craft this, then you want it, right?
There's like, there's as many ways, as we say, there's many ways to roam.
No, wait, all roads lead to roam, right?
And that's true in this game as well.
Where multiple items can lead to the same idea.
So if you don't happen to find a balloon, say, you know, you can do this instead.
Which is cool, no?
Fuck, I wish this house was working, dude.
Why are you not working?
Is it technically working now?
Get out of here.
Get rid of this fucking thing.
It sucks.
Teleport!
Wow.
Why can't it put me in a new place?
Come on, man.
Put me in a... Oh, that's an enemy.
That's also an enemy.
Let me get my bearings here.
Hold on now.
Hey.
Oh, the P is effective.
A cross necklace.
Nice!
I think I have one of those already, though.
Wait, is that also a... Hold on.
Maybe not.
Wait, I never looted this.
Gold.
Cool.
Is that a strange plant?
Oops, I just released the lava!
But I have a million Omni Potions.
Wait, Omni Potions?
What am I talking about?
Where did I put them?
Here?
No.
Oh, don't tell me they got sorted into the chests.
God damn it!
Anyway, I don't want to be down here anyway.
Let's go back.
We gotta go... Let's go to the temple and see if it's open by now.
You know what?
Let's bring the sundial.
I feel like the sundial and that temple can be sort of connected, you know?
You know, fucking Egyptians and shit, they loved that sun.
They were making huge sundials out of structures and shit.
Maybe that... Burger!
Nice.
That's another major improvement to stats later on.
Which is something I enjoy immensely.
I am an enjoyer of the burger.
Hold on.
Yeah.
Where exactly was it?
There.
Oh, it's still quite a far away.
We gotta use our dinosaur here.
Dinosauatu.
Bum, bum, bum.
Okay.
Look how aggressive it looks when I ride on this thing.
Okay, we're not there yet.
By the way, I still have those items.
I got two of the tablet fragments or something like that.
And honestly, I have no clue how I got that.
I just had to sneeze real bad there.
Dude, my allergies are fucking killing me nowadays.
It's insane.
Even with medicine and shit, it's pure hell.
I wouldn't wish allergies on my worst enemy.
It really is just the worst.
Like, after sneezing just now, I actually have trouble breathing.
Like, that's the thing.
I have to really breathe hard right now just to breathe normally.
It really sucks.
That's like the thing.
In Denmark, it's shitty weather all year round, right?
But in the summer, we get these few precious weeks of great weather.
But at the same time, I can't really enjoy it.
Because I'm fucked during that time.
It's just the worst combo.
God damn it, I can't get in.
What's making that sound?
Is that the Leesart?
Leesart?
You idiot.
Give me your things.
If I hold up the necklace, like in that movie, The Mummy, maybe something will happen.
Oh no, he holds that up to the mummy itself, I think.
Spoiler alert.
Bring them Frasier's best, I would say.
Armored skeletons.
I do wonder if these guys dropped something new down here now.
Oh, that's what I'm gonna do.
Let's try the turtle shells that I found.
Turtle... wait, what?
Must have been material, right?
Yeah.
Alright, my dude.
Remind me again about these turtle shells.
There.
Right.
It's chlorophyte.
Okay.
Here's what we're gonna do.
First things first, close the door.
Go back up here.
Shake his hand.
There you go.
And then, we look on the map for chlorophyte.
I think I remember where I saw it.
Somewhere in this region.
Oricalcum.
Web.
Titanium.
There.
It's very hard to spot.
You see that?
Can I find something closer to the surface?
Let's see over here.
Chlorophyte.
Beehive?
Here?
Huh.
Just do this with the mouse.
Maybe we're too far out.
Wait, wait.
Moon glow.
Fuck it, I'm gonna go there where I saw it.
I can teleport here, right?
So, it's actually fine.
I'm gonna try and see what the deal was with that chlorophyte.
I don't think I'm able to mine it, but I have to remember why that is and what I need for it.
I need to see this situation again here.
Let's see.
Chlorophyte.
God, it's so hard to spot.
Honestly, I already forgot what it looked like.
God damn it.
Is it down here?
Like, what precise shade of green is it?
There's so many shades!
Do I see a chlorophyte?
There!
We're taking that.
So that's...
straight down, basically.
Wait, did I just...
Sapphire squirrel?
Excuse me?
Ha!
Interesting.
Oh.
Thank you.
Ah, these fucking guys.
Just making my blood boil.
Should be...
Wait, is it that right there?
No.
So it should be right here.
Sort of.
There it is!
Right there.
Quick nature's grit?
Hold on, I need to...
Oh, nature's gift!
Right.
Okay, so why...
Okay.
Chlorophyte.
Um, the only thing I can think of...
It doesn't even say anything.
I think I may need titanium pickaxe for that.
It's like the next logical step, right?
I have an orichalcum run right now.
It's maybe just not enough.
We need some titanium up in this bitch.
Or...
Let's smelt.
Smelt it all.
Uh, stack it.
And then put this back.
There you go.
Now.
Uh, can I make...
Shit.
I have to remind myself how many it costs.
So, we gotta go to Jeremy.
Also, I forgot about the enchanted sundial test that I wanted to perform.
Let's see here.
Hey, I can make it.
I can actually make it.
Where do these enemies come from?
Get off my property.
Oh, I keep thinking this is an enemy.
It's just my little pigman.
Where have I seen a pigman before?
I feel like this design right here is familiar to me.
I've seen this in some media.
Maybe.
It's just the face looks...
And again, pigs are kind of very well-known creatures.
Uh, so yeah.
Okay, I need that specialized animal.
There we go.
Oh, wait a minute.
I can also make...
Nah, I don't want that.
Give me this.
It doesn't say able to mine whatever like this one does.
So, let's experiment.
Probably, this is just a waste.
I guess it's not because I wanted to upgrade anyway.
165, 190.
Yeah, this is definitely an upgrade.
Just from a pure raw mining power perspective here.
Uh, I'm gonna use the teleportation system.
Oh my god.
Fuck off!
Okay, let's go down here.
Why am I so slow?
Get rid of that golf ball.
Just running around with a golf ball in my pocket.
Oh, wait.
This is not it.
We take this way.
I'm probably passing some chlorophyte on the way, but honestly, I can't fucking see that shit.
I know where there is some.
I'm getting it.
Fuck.
Yeah.
God damn it.
I mean, I should have known.
It doesn't say, uh, can mine chlorophyte, right?
So, I don't know, man.
All right.
Uh, what's the next thing I want to try?
What else can I try here?
What item?
Let me actually see if I can make other things.
Hey, Bob.
Look at this here again.
Remind me what else I can make out of this.
Uh, sword, repeater, war axe, chainsaw.
Can I please talk to fucking Bob for a second, guys?
Huh?
I am so exhausted from having to fight all the time.
Stop.
Any of it say...
Orykal...
No, not Orykal.
Where is Bob?
Wait a minute.
Motherfucker.
Did they kill him?
Where's my sundial?
Is it working?
Wait.
Oh, wait, I can only do it one day a week or something, right?
Look at my pig companion.
Just...
Oh, he's gone now, I guess.
How many died?
Oh,
no, close the door.
Oh, it doesn't matter, the fucking guy is dead anyway.
When does he come back?
Dude, when are you back?
I need you.
Oh, I'm getting a headache, man.
Close that door.
Click this button.
Uh, delete, get rid of the golf ball.
How did you just...
Didn't I just fucking close the door?
For God, I hate this.
Did I not just close that fucking door?
Uh, throw the silt away, I don't even want to convert it.
What's that sound?
Oh, it's the cloud, okay.
Uh, no, I want to pee instead.
Pee everywhere.
Where did that guy just go?
Did he just fuck off?
Weird.
Okay.
Uh...
Get out of the guide.
Get back here.
Did he maybe respawn somewhere else by chance?
No, he would tell me in the chat, right?
Hmm.
I don't know what to do, man.
I don't know what the next step is here.
This is very confusing.
And the guide is just repeating some bullshit to me.
About some mushrooms.
Okay, you know what?
That's what I can do.
The last thing he told me of any note was about mushrooms glowing on the surface.
I'm gonna try and find them.
Last time I tried going right.
Now I'm gonna try going left.
And I'm gonna go all the way to the sea.
See if we can't find a mushroom that is glowing.
And I think we are also...
It's morning now, I think.
But maybe it's easier to see while it's still a little bit dark out.
Let's try that.
Let's see if anything mind-blowing will happen when we find this mushroom.
Also, I wonder how big the mushroom is gonna be.
Like, is it gonna be a small glowing one or...
a really big one?
Like, how big are we talking, right?
I'm guessing it's not gonna be in this biome.
But then again, who knows?
The Sean has arrived!
That's a good sign.
That means maybe the guide will come back soon.
No, that's berries.
Okay.
Okay, it's still storming here.
No, those are just my gravestones.
Oh, what's that, what's that, what's that?
Oh!
It's just a glow stick.
It looked like something else.
Oh, I'm frostbitten.
Ah, nice.
Look at this.
A gentle snow.
Interrupted by enemies.
God forbid I get a moment's rest, you know?
Uh...
I'm not...
I'm really trying to look here.
I don't see any mushrooms.
What is that right there?
Just some kind of stone, a spiky stone or something.
Wait, oh, he's just confused?
I did say on the surface, right?
Anything here?
Uh, hold on.
I kind of forgot I had this guy here.
Hey, my dude!
Isaac!
Lovely morning, wouldn't you say?
Is there something you needed?
This is actually a lovely place.
I love that there's no enemies.
You can sell a safe...
multiplayer item, I think.
Now, what is that?
Scott has arrived!
Perfect.
Armor penetration from melee weapons, huh?
Melee weapons have armor penetration.
I don't know if it works on my fucking cool whip.
It's obviously a melee weapon.
But then again, maybe not.
It does say summon damage, but it's obviously a melee weapon?
It's a fucking whip.
Uh...
I think maybe it would say something here, right?
If it did.
Uh, hold on.
Can I actually...
Wait, what?
Oh, get rid of that?
Let me see something here.
This is technically a melee weapon, right?
21 melee damage.
100% axe power, 600 hammer power?
What if I...
Yeah, maybe it wouldn't factor into this calculation here, because it's just going to penetrate through armor.
You know?
Maybe it wouldn't show here, actually.
However, when you get a damage buff, it actually does increase the number you see on this tooltip.
So that's why I was expecting that.
But maybe that doesn't count for some reason, because it's...
an axe?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Ayo!
Isaac!
What else do we sell?
Just the basics of basics.
A drumstick.
Playable next to a drumset?
You know what?
Why not?
Let's try it.
No enemies?
This is the perfect time.
Maybe I have to have it equipped?
Look.
Oh, cool.
So I guess all...
Snare?
I guess all these are like musical terms.
I actually don't know anything about music.
I know what's snare.
I've heard that before.
Floor tom?
These are probably like...
drumming terms.
Yeah.
I wonder if I can do the...
you know, two cymbals and a snare, or whatever it's called.
Where's
the...
I don't know.
Alright, that's kind of cool, I guess.
Also, I guess a multiplayer item thingy.
It wouldn't surprise me if some people out there actually play some music with this.
You know, it seems possible to create a song with it.
I mean, you have different...
things you...
Quack!
You have different sounds you can make, right?
And whenever there's different sounds to be made, people make music.
That's a fact.
Blueberries.
Quackies?
You get to die.
This right here is so weird.
What is making that sound?
Septimus.
You can't see my face right now, but it's actually a face of rage.
I am filled with hatred when I look at this guy.
There we go.
Trap him in there.
You are not to go in the water.
Okay, Isaac.
Good thing you closed the door behind you.
Don't let him out of there.
Don't let him into the water.
No!
Motherfucker!
Isaac!
I hate that sound.
Okay, any mushrooms over here?
I was looking for mushrooms, right?
Here's what I'm gonna do now.
As an act, as a symbolic act of my frustration of finding this mushroom.
The Elder Slime has left.
Nice!
That just increased my spirits.
I'm in a better mood already.
A squid.
Oh, wait.
It gave me black ink.
Cool.
I'm gonna walk out into the sea.
With the musics blasting.
Wait, what do we have here?
Hold on now.
Wait a minute.
I was about to kill myself.
But now I'm intrigued.
What is this?
Would you look at that?
Weird!
Cool, though.
Man, this is not being held together by much, huh?
Drain it!
Oh, if you're ever in doubt whether or not to drain, the answer is always yes.
Drain it.
A chest!
A shark!
I can't think, just take things.
Ah, fuck, I don't have time.
Ah, get up, get up, get up.
Get up!
Another chest.
Ah, let, ah...
Armored water walking...
Whoa!
I think I had one of those before.
Um...
Okay.
That was fun.
Having this little inlet there, or whatever you call it.
I am gonna kill myself, though.
As a symbolic gesture of my inability to find mushrooms on the surface that was very clearly promised to me.
A shark fin I got.
Suffer.
Because I'm gonna call it here anyway.
I'm gonna teleport back to the main island now.
Well, the spawn point, I guess.
I'm developing a headache, honestly.
Wait, why did I drop gold?
I put it all in my thingy.
Did I not?
Well, I dropped 12 silver, who cares.
Whew!
I think I need to take a pill.
That was something.
Okay, I'm gonna open chat.
Uh, wait a minute, let me...
Let me do this in a smart way.
Yeah, that's fine.
Alright, I can see you now.
What's up, people?
Oliver, a big Terraria YouTuber was in here asking about your progress.
Oh, yeah?
What'd you tell him?
I'm struggling.
Nice work on the pirate invasion.
I feel like that's the only nice work I did today.
I honestly, I'm pretty aimless right now in this game.
I feel like, uh...
Expert Terraria seems ambitious.
Yeah, I think I agree.
I should not have picked expert.
I kinda regret it.
So I don't know what the next step is in the game, but I can theorize, right?
So far, my impressions are that most of the progression in this game is tied to the bosses.
And it's not clear at all which bosses are supposed to be fought in which order at all, because at one point you'll be fighting something that is extremely easy.
And next up, you just get smashed, like there's no fucking chance.
And you don't know how to get to the boss?
Like I had this item that summoned it, maybe I think I crafted it, but how are you supposed to know to make that item and in which order?
And for me, the bosses themselves are probably the worst thing about this game.
I don't like fighting them.
I wish I could never fight them.
So I feel like I... and they're so difficult too.
They're just not fun for me.
The bosses are just not fun.
So that's... I think that's what's preventing me from progressing.
That's my theory right now.
Expert was a mistake.
Yeah, yeah.
Now I'll be legendary if you continue.
Here's the thing.
Yeah, so I'm trying to draw parallels here now to Rainworld, because I also struggled a lot in that game, right?
But that game had a different kind of difficulty, where you're sort of this helpless creature in this hostile world, right?
And most of the time you sort of knew what the idea was, or actually, maybe you even didn't, right?
There were many times in some of the campaigns where you didn't know what to do.
But I feel like at least the surviving part and getting lore out of that was like a really nice reward.
You know what I mean?
Like, that's really motivating.
I don't know if I can say the same about this game.
Are you watching hockey?
No, not at all.
I don't know anything about hockey, bro.
And I'm not calling you bro, just because your name is bro.
What, things are fun then?
I really love exploring caves in this game.
Caving?
Finding new items?
Building?
I really like building.
You probably knew that by now.
But it's like constantly being interrupted by random shit, you know, like enemies everywhere.
Expert looked promising in the beginning, unfortunately having trouble.
Yeah, it's really like... I do admit, maybe I'm just really terrible at this game.
I mean, it's fine.
Maybe I just suck, you know, it's very possible.
I'm not an expert at all.
So...
I mean...
No, I wouldn't say ooh, but yeah.
I like some sports.
Esports.
Haha, Starcraft.
Didn't know you're an excellent drummer, boy.
I'm not Diego, I don't know anything about drums.
I can't play any instrument.
Unfortunately, I have a blow-high.
The all-one.
Nice.
I was thinking of getting one myself.
I have a friend who keeps talking about it, and she's very adamant about the blow-high.
Wait, where are you from, the all-one?
Expert can be really hard, especially if you don't have a great idea on the progression of the game.
Yeah, so here's the thing.
I already knew going in, because people told me this, that this game is heavily reliant on the player looking up things on a V-key, right?
Here's the thing.
I didn't go into this game with an adamant mindset of I don't want to use the wiki at all.
That's not how I approach things.
Honestly, for me, it's just like I see this game on Steam.
It's a video game.
I want to play the video game, right?
And I just want to play it as it is, you know?
I feel it's kind of silly if I have to use external tools to try to understand the game I'm playing.
So that's like the mindset that I have.
I would never be against using the wiki at all times or something, you know?
If a game is actually made for that and if you cannot play it without it.
Well, of course, in that case, you have to do it, right?
It's 100% possible to beat the game without the wiki.
Yeah, I guess it is.
I mean, I imagine it is.
And my guess is I just have to beat all the bosses, right?
That's my guess on that.
You beat the game without the wiki?
That's nice, man.
But did you also enjoy the bosses?
Because I think it's a bit easier, maybe, like motivationally.
Expert just requires more knowledge of the game.
Huh.
Do you mean like, what type of knowledge are you talking about?
Do you mean like, what to do next?
Or is it more like knowledge as in more experience and more skill?
Knowing how to fight.
Is that what you mean?
To answer your question, I'm from England.
Ah!
Okay.
So I guess you also have...
I guess many countries have Ikeas nowadays.
The Swedish are invading the rest of the world.
Tactics?
Hmm.
Okay.
Knowledge as in tactics.
I see.
Okay.
Yeah.
I mean, I know I'm definitely not doing things optimally.
There's always things to improve, right?
More experience, what to do to have a high chance to win?
Yeah.
Much of the knowledge is what you would consider cheesy.
Really?
What do you mean?
Hold on.
Are you saying that the optimal strategy... Okay.
Are you saying that most of the strategies in this game...
where the game is made to be cheesed?
As in, sort of, you have to cheat the game?
In a way?
I actually am looking for a yes or no answer to that.
It's okay if you say yes or no.
The game isn't made to be cheesed.
Okay, okay.
Then I misunderstood.
Sorry.
Okay.
Gotcha.
No.
Okay, perfect.
I was about to say that sounded weird, if that was the case.
So I had a little trouble believing that.
To me, it's way more fun to cheese it anyway.
That's a good point.
Some games that are, like, really punishing...
when you finally figure out a way to just, you know, cheese it, it actually feels amazing.
It's like getting back at the game in a way.
You know what I mean?
Cheese just means taking advantage of knowledge.
I see.
Okay, okay.
I think my problem with my skill in this game is that I can't understand what's happening on the screen.
Most of the time, it's so chaotic.
That's also why I always suck at bullet-hell-type games.
When there's too much stuff on the screen, it's just overwhelming.
You know?
And this is a me thing.
I have trouble focusing on that.
Focusing on dodging things when there's just projectiles everywhere, and the boss moves in unpredictable patterns when you don't know it.
And you only get a couple shots at it because you only have a couple items, so it puts pressure on you to actually try and beat it.
You only get a couple chances.
It's very little room for error here.
Especially because it doesn't feel like the armor you make makes any difference at all.
You know?
I feel like I get three, four shots no matter what armor I'm wearing.
So it's kind of crazy.
But maybe that is just because I'm playing on Expert, and it's like...
I chose that, right?
So...
Pirate Invasion was 100% cheese.
Was it?
I guess so.
Not exactly cheese?
I would say this game is definitely...
way more difficult than Minecraft ever was.
I mean, Minecraft was hard at times, of course.
But you know what I loved about Minecraft?
It was like focused on the exploration constantly, you know what I mean?
That was actually a boss in Minecraft.
Spoiler, I guess.
But I guess everyone's played that at the very end there.
What would you say is your favorite genre in gaming?
Hmm...
I mean, if I...
That's a good question.
I really like good lore.
I like a good story.
You know?
So if a good story is being told, whether I am the one finding the story or it's being told to me...
Either one is fine.
If it's a great story, I'm all in.
I like that.
I like good stories.
So RPGs are usually a big thing for me.
I really like The Last of Us as an example.
You get fed a really great story there.
That's a great example of a story that's just being given to you, right?
And there's some cool action in there as well.
That sort of stuff.
But probably my favorite thing, but just purely based statistically here on how much time I've spent on it.
I've said this before, it's got to be World of Warcraft.
And I know that's not a genre, but it kind of is.
It created a genre on its own, right?
Nowadays I don't play it as much because it's not that good anymore, but back then it was the tits, you know?
I like that and also RTS games.
I play a shit ton of Starcraft.
It's my game I can play forever.
Love Starcraft.
Whether it be a building on Redstone Stream or Redstone Stream, bosses and enemies will intrude and make sure everyone is happy.
Will intrude.
I don't understand what you mean by that lightning buff.
When you say Redstone, are you talking about Minecraft here specifically or...
or Terraria?
Because I use the word Redstone in this game as well to describe the mechanisms.
I have not played Undertale.
It's on my list.
I'm looking forward to that.
Everyone is praising it.
I've heard good stuff about that ever since, well, it came out.
It's an indie game.
I don't think there is a cheese because there is no intended way to do things.
You win your fights through whatever means you can come up with.
Yeah, okay.
Actually, I have an example of that.
So, remember the skeleton boss that I fought?
I had so much trouble with that.
And then I realized, if I was building places to walk on, you know, make it straight, the fight became much easier.
Like, I had to make...
Like, I made platforms and then I went a little higher and I made another platform so I could jump between them.
That actually made it easier, but I hated doing that.
I felt like I was cheating by doing that.
And I don't want to do that again because it feels terrible.
I don't want to take it down after.
It's tedious.
I feel like...
I feel like it's unintended in a way.
Oh, you're all saying big brain cook?
But here's the thing.
That's like the thing I hate the most.
Not achieved.
Why take it down?
Ah, because I'm weird like that, man.
I...
I hate when things don't look nice.
You know what I mean?
Like, if there's... this is why I hate my railway so much.
There's just this ugly railway in my world.
Am I crazy?
I feel like it's like in Minecraft when you destroy a tree, right?
For me, I have to destroy the whole route so the entire tree disappears.
It's not satisfying to me if it doesn't disappear entirely.
Does anyone resonate with that, or...?
It's totally like a looks thing.
You're the same way, player.
Okay, I guess I'm not the only one in that case.
Railway is good-looking, what do you mean?
Thanks, Mr. Seeker.
I mean, I did spend a lot of time on it.
It's kind of pretty, I guess.
Grab the sun.
Moon with your mouse.
Wait, really?
Oh!
I thought you kept making references to...
Mad Max.
Fury Road.
Awesome.
That's a nice little easter egg.
The tree thing is very common on the server.
We shun people who don't cut down the whole tree in public area.
That's what I'm talking about!
Good job, Gen and people on that server.
I like that.
I approve of that.
That's awesome.
Wait, did the music change?
Did the music just change?
I think it does.
Do you have a favorite movie?
I do.
It's...
Black Swan.
Favorite movie of all time.
And then after that, Contact with Jodie Foster.
Love those movies.
There used to be a glitch involving grabbing the sun slash moon where it allowed you to skip events like blood moons.
No way!
What?
That's funny.
Astrophysics nerd shit?
Yeah, okay.
I agree.
That one is.
Contact is definitely... It's like... It's such a good...
story, you know?
I love that sort of stuff.
I love aliens when there's no aliens.
Do you know what I mean?
Like, I don't want to see the aliens.
I mean, I do love the movie Alien, but...
I love not seeing them and having to imagine them.
Yeah, that's why I named my pets Jodie.
In Minecraft.
Jodie Foster.
How are you guys doing on this Friday, huh?
Are you having a good day today?
What are you guys' plans this weekend?
I'm curious.
Are you doing anything interesting?
Are you going out to touch grass?
Still working?
Okay.
Very nice, I guess.
Or not.
Depending on your...
Did you get some awesome aurora borealis lately?
With the solar storm?
I heard there was some, but I actually never went out and checked.
Yeah.
I think that thing just flew by me, in a way.
I did not catch any of that.
I'm having a good day, but I have a lot of word.
A lot of word?
I'm attending a grad party with a friend on Saturday, though.
Oh, nice!
Congratulations to that friend, I guess.
I have a bad case of diarrhea.
That sucks, man!
I'm sorry to hear that.
I hope you get better soon.
Horse camping!
Wait, Pathfinder?
Lena?
Is that...
That's a tabletop game, isn't it?
What the hell is horse camping?
Is that just going camping with a horse?
Kaylee the Alien is having the best day of her life.
Nice!
That's good.
I had too many clouds for the Aurora.
That sucks.
You didn't touch grass?
Dude, if I touch grass, I'm going to be dying.
I have the craziest allergies.
I literally do not want to touch any grass.
I have to catch up on my Japanese homework.
Nice!
How come you're learning Japanese?
Is it just for fun, or do you need it for work or something?
Jake tracks!
You're in the middle of the U.S.
and could see it!
Yeah, I did hear that we had one of the biggest solar storms in a long time.
So I'm not surprised that...
all those charged particles...
spiraled in and created a little show for people.
4D Golf kicks my ass.
Love mini-golf, and it takes the cake as hard as so far.
Really?
You're getting your ass kicked by a golfing game.
That just sounds funny to me, Sir Frank.
But, uh...
Nice!
I've actually never played golf.
I would love to try it.
Hopefully not in the summer, though, because there's lots of grass there, and that's bad.
It's hard to get the horse in the tent.
Wait, is the horse camping thing a joke?
Is that actually real?
Or do you mean, like, you go out there on a horse...
and camp?
Because that sounds badass.
Roxia.
I'm seeing so many new people in the chat today...
that I don't recognize.
It's awesome.
Welcome, guys.
And girls, and everyone in between.
We had snow recently, and then it was hot again.
Yeah, it sounds like the weather in Denmark.
It's very up and down.
You can't really expect anything.
It's not consistent.
Hi, Oliver.
Heard of oxygen not included.
Actually, I have.
I wanted to put it on my list.
It's a 2D game.
And it's...
It's a management game, right?
I'm not gonna say similar to Factorio...
but just similar in the fact that it's a management game.
And it's like finding optimizations like that.
Sounds fun.
By the way, I've seen so many people suggest 4D Golf by now.
Are you guys... is this a joke or something?
Is that game actually good?
Like, is it a PC game, or...?
I mean, it's on my list, because people suggested it, but...
It just doesn't sound like something people would suggest for some reason.
I don't know why.
It's good.
It's kind of a meme.
It's so good.
Okay.
Meme game.
You would like it as an astrophysicist?
That sounds worrying, in a way.
I don't know why, but that's fun.
Interesting.
Satisfactory.
That's a 3D version of Factorio, right?
I've heard that one is really good as well, and they keep making updates for it.
Really good support.
It's releasing this year!
Maybe I'll finally try it then.
I also know that VRising recently released.
I've been eyeing that game as well.
Thinking of playing it.
But I wanted to wait until it was out.
Same devs as Hyperbolica.
I don't know Hyperbolica.
I haven't played that one.
Gregory.
Did you know there's two Minecraft spin-off games?
I know there's one called Minecraft Dungeons.
And I'm not sure about the other one.
If that is indeed one of the spin-offs you're thinking of.
Hey, no soup.
You love the inscription playthrough.
That's nice.
I'm loving that game too.
That game is fantastic.
Speaking of, I'm going to release an episode after this of course.
What's your favorite game you played off the channel?
Oh, that's gotta be...
Well, if we just exclude World of Warcraft and Starcraft.
Probably...
Well, that's a hard question.
Probably The Last of Us.
One and two.
Both of them.
Utterly fantastic.
Maybe I even like the second one more.
It's so close though.
Such good games.
Minecraft, Minecraft Dungeons and Minecraft Legends.
Okay.
I did actually hear the word Minecraft Legends before.
I'm not sure what it's about though.
There's a Minecraft story mode.
Yeah, I heard about that too, Mr. Sika.
I don't think there's a community Terraria world.
No soup.
But there is a Minecraft one.
And it's awesome.
Sometimes I peek into the official Minecraft channel and...
and then I promptly close it again.
But other times I peek in and I just see amazing constructions.
That's like a whole sub-community of people in there with their own...
little, you know, thing.
You ever play on the server?
Maybe.
Maybe you never noticed.
Maybe I have a house there.
Maybe I'm just planting doubt among all of you right now.
What do you mean, maybe?
Is this the start or the end?
Smooka, it's the end.
I'm sorry.
It is the end.
I'm just sitting here chatting a bit.
Before getting out to get some food.
I'm getting so many AFK journey ads.
What is that?
What is an AFK journey ad?
I plant the giant diorite cube.
What if I told you I'm actually Jim?
I've been writing in chat this entire time.
It's me.
It's been me all along.
Remember that title?
It was me all along?
That's what I was trying to say.
I'm going to prove it now.
I'm going to write, I am Oliver.
Look, hold on.
Here it comes.
Just typing.
I am Oliver.
And enter.
Look, there it is.
Jen, you're amazing.
Thanks so much for playing along with that one.
I'm just kidding, of course.
That explains a lot, does it?
Oh, no.
This is getting a little silly.
By the way, thinking about the whole Twitch thing I talked about at the beginning.
Like the switch to Twitch.
The switch to Twitch.
There are so many games that also have Twitch integration.
And I wonder if there's any of you that know a game, because some of you suggested having like a night where we play games together.
Is there like a really nice game for that sort of thing that has that capability?
Because that shit sounds fun.
Does Noida have Twitch integration?
I know that's a roguelite game.
Oh, Jackbox, yeah, Jackbox is a classic.
I play that in real life with my friends all the time.
I guess, yeah, I guess you could play that with Twitch.
That would be fun, actually.
Wouldn't it?
With Noida, you can have chat spent channel points to mess with your world.
Really?
What the heck?
That does sound fun.
Isaac, you mean the Binding of Isaac, right?
That's a game that my real life friend has been raving about forever.
He has like 350 hours or something in that game.
Which is insane because he's very critical of games, you know?
He plays very few games.
So whenever he plays something, you know it's good.
And he's been playing that a lot.
Hi Oliver, he doesn't for know.
Any plans to play Talos Principle 2?
Moridini, he's asking whether or not I have plans.
Oh yeah, he said that in English.
Yes, I'm planning on playing that, of course.
I absolutely love the first one.
I need to play the second.
It's not even a question, of course.
Definitely.
It's super addicting, Havish.
That's the thing I like about roguelites.
That's the thing I really liked about Inscription 2.
There's a bit of roguelite element there, at least in some parts of the game, and it's awesome.
Wait, wait, wait!
What about Disco Elysium?
Well, Roxia, I already played that off stream some years ago.
So unfortunately, it's not really a game that I want to replay.
But it's really good.
It's awesome.
I played it back before they added voice lines, though.
So I was sort of voicing everything in my mind.
And honestly, I think that may have made it funnier.
I don't know.
I haven't tried the new version with all the voice lines.
But sometimes things are funnier in your mind, you know, when you don't hear it.
Because you imagine the funniest situation in any given moment.
Disco Elysium is incredible.
Yeah.
I have not played.
I mean, so no soup.
I've played the very beginning of Elden Ring.
Like, I honestly forget how many hours, but I think it's like between five and seven hours or something.
Plus minus two.
Who knows?
The very beginning area.
I don't remember where I went there, but I just sort of, you know, went around there.
But I want to play it when the expansion comes out.
Then I'm going all in on Elden Ring.
Really been getting the itch to play some soul stuff after I finished Bloodborne recently.
You probably get swamped with suggestions all the time, but I'd like to suggest a game that has gone kind of under the radar.
Humanity, a puzzle game heavily inspired by lemmings.
I don't know who lemmings is, but I do like puzzle games.
Also, isn't humanity a strategy game?
Or am I thinking of something else?
But OK, let me write that down also.
Humanity.
I'm just adding it to my notepad list later.
I just don't have it open right now.
I'm going to add it later.
Have you played Stardew Valley?
I played a little bit with a friend of mine in real life.
Just some co-op.
I think I played a couple hours of it.
Seemed really fun.
Very relaxing.
Very nice.
I want to play more of it someday.
Have you heard about the Chinese company Ligma?
Bruh.
Stop.
Don't don't say it.
I mean, say it, say it.
Lemmings is an animal.
Lemmings is so... What?
Lemmings as in plural of lemming.
I have no idea what the fuck you guys are talking about.
What kind of animal is lemmings?
Oh wait, what kind of animal is a lemming?
Wait, really?
You should try up dog.
Oh yeah?
Tell me about up dog.
Let's hear it.
Lemmings are rodents.
Super cute.
Ha!
By the way, after I finished a game I'm playing right now on the channel, I don't want to spoil too much, of course, but there was an animal in that game that I didn't think was real because the name just sounded like bullshit.
After the game finished, I looked it up.
It's a real fucking animal.
And it's actually really cute.
It's an actual animal.
It's amazing.
Small, insane rodents.
Sounds like something that I would like.
You should check the actual lemings game.
Okay, I'm gonna write that too.
I put it on the list.
By the way, the list that's on this code right now is in no particular order.
It's just randomized.
There is no order here.
Oliver, how did you enjoy that game?
I loved it.
My first game of that type, and you know what I mean.
And it is incredible.
Definitely one of the most memorable games I've ever played.
I finished it already, of course.
Yeah.
Definitely.
Barty and Angel.
Yep.
I guess that must have been really funny for the people that knew that that was a real animal.
Oh my god.
Hey, RayJCard, it's rare that you get to make a stream.
This is really nice.
It is.
I really enjoy hanging out and talking to you guys.
It's so much fun.
You know the game Autonauts?
Actually, I don't.
But I don't know most games.
Do you know how many games are out there?
There are so many games.
And now people are talking about Animal Well 2 being amazing.
So that's just another game to add to my list.
It's never ending.
What's your music taste?
I listen to everything.
And maybe that's a cop-out answer, Simon.
But it's more... it's like I go in faces.
I listen to certain genres and faces a lot.
And then some other time I change to something else.
I'm really big into rap.
I love 90s and 2000s rap.
Hip-hop.
Stuff like that.
I really love electronic music.
And some rock.
I love everything.
I love good music.
I also had a phase where I listened to a lot of swing music.
Because I was doing...
Because I was dancing swing.
Like Lindy Hop.
If you guys know that.
I was going crazy with that for a time.
Oliver, have you heard of the hit game Noida?
No, I haven't.
What's that?
I'm kidding.
Can
you make your list publicly available?
It is publicly available, the old one.
It's on the Discord.
But it's in the games channel pinned as a notepad file with my...
I know it's not very optimal.
I think there's a better way of doing this, probably.
Having some online list that just gets updated automatically.
Whatever I make a change, you know?
That's probably better.
I know it's not optimal.
It's kind of a...
You know?
Man, good music is the best!
Exactly, Serix!
It's just the best!
How is swing dancing?
It's really fun.
You need a partner though, mostly.
To dance with.
Otherwise it's not as fun.
But it's really fun in the way that you just...
You have this set of different moves and you just combine them randomly.
So you have a leader and a follower, right?
And the leader just chooses whatever.
And when you get good together, you can sort of make all kinds of funny things happen.
It's a lot of fun.
You can try and google Lindy Hop.
Swing.
It's cool.
I want to learn swing dancing but I don't have partners.
Just go to a swing lesson.
Many people go there solo.
And then they just dance with the people that are there.
And then you exchange partners and you dance.
It's a lot of fun.
Can you sing karaoke someday?
Hell nah, bruh.
By the way, I love that your name is bruh.
Because it's so natural for me to add that at the end.
I have a terrible singing voice.
The way you describe swing dancing honestly sounds kind of like jazz.
With the lead and everything.
Maybe it is kind of similar.
I don't know a lot about jazz.
I like jazz music.
But I don't know any specifics of how it's...
How it's done, you know?
In practice.
I want to swing partners.
But I don't have a partner.
Nice.
You should sing I Will Always Love You.
Should I?
Should I really though?
I'm not sure.
Swing music is a style of jazz.
Yeah, it is.
Right now.
No, actually right now I think I actually got to go make some food.
I need to eat.
For some reason I'm not even that hungry but I know I should be hungry.
Because I haven't eaten in a while.
So my body is playing tricks on me.
I need to force myself to eat.
Oliver is in the swinger.
He's a vacuumer.
Damn right.
Vacuuming all day.
Sing me a lullaby so I can fall asleep.
No.
Some other time.
Isn't it really late in Denmark?
It's 21.51 here.
So almost 10.
So yeah, it is kind of late for dinner.
We usually eat dinner around 6.7.
But I ate a late lunch.
We had lunch at like 1.
A lot of your speaking today had the demon inflection in your voice.
It was concerning.
Really?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
But thanks.
So since you actually take suggestions from us, is there a game you enjoy that you'd like something similar to?
Oh, that's a good question.
Yes, give me World of Warcraft 2.
If you can dish that up.
I will forever sing your praises.
That's the song I will sing.
Your praises.
Yeah, okay, here's a real one.
Give me a game similar to Outer Wilds.
Actually, just give me Outer Wilds 2.
Or maybe don't.
It's already perfect as it is.
Don't really change it, I guess.
Blake, twice if there's a demon in you, Oliver.
Okay, hold on.
There.
You know we can't do that, Oliver.
Oh, man, that's just that's a funny sentence.
I love that.
Actually, it's true.
There's nothing like Outer Wilds, is there?
I've been watching other people play it just because I want to play it again, but I can't.
I can't!
So I'm watching other people go through it.
I'm sorry Oliver, I can't do that.
Yeah,
what is Mobius Digital even working on nowadays?
You guys know?
Are they actually making something new?
Are they cooking?
Actually, I'm not watching Elise, Simon.
I'm watching the original watch, usually.
Not because I don't like the idea of a shortened version, it's just I hate missing out on things, I guess.
Probably cooking, they need money.
Oh, really?
After that, is Outer Wilds massively successful?
Or maybe it's like one of those situations like, what's that movie called?
Blade Runner, you know?
Blade Runner bombed back when it released in the 80s or whatever.
But since then it's become a cult classic and everybody loves it.
So maybe it's a similar thing.
I don't know if it did well when it launched.
I have no idea.
Real and true.
Hey, a fellow Asman enjoyer.
I love it.
DDLC is a game of all time.
What is DDLC?
How many hours do you have in a while?
Rough estimate?
I wouldn't measure that in hours, probably years.
And if in years, probably one year.
But that is the most... pull a statistic out of your ass statistic I've ever pulled.
So it could be less than that.
It could also be more, I don't know.
It's a lot.
But that was back when I was... but a young lad skipping school to go kill trolls in Stranglethorn, you know?
It's probably not a whole year.
That's insane.
Probably way less.
But it's a lot.
It's a lot.
Alright guys, I'm gonna be out of here.
I need to eat.
Thank you so much for watching.
I may actually end up at some point, if I get too stuck in this game, ask for advice.
It may be the time.
Because... or maybe I should... yeah, I don't know.
I'll think about it.
But yeah.
We'll see.
Until next time.
Have a great weekend, okay?
And don't you dare have a bad weekend.
You better enjoy it.
I wanna see smiles all around.
Bye-bye.
Inscription now.